If you are going to proceed, do you plan to organize new activities?
Do you plan to organize new activities in the future? Do you plan to organize new activities in the future?
Do you plan to hold new activities in the future?
Are you planning to hold future activities?
Are you planning to organize future activities?
Here we go. This is Talky Abert MC taking a bath. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I am. This is a talk show in which we invite guests who lead the Japanese subculture scene of movies, music, and anime, and delve into their charms.
Yes.
So, we are back in the spacious studio with a pin microphone.
Yes, it is a beautiful studio. A beautiful studio.
I wonder if they use the budget to buy and lose Pachinko (Japanese pinball).
What do you mean?
Suddenly the budget disappears and then comes back.
No, no, no, it's fine. Slingshot.
This time, we have a great environment to work in.
It's just that the studio is back again. Just because of the difference in the studio, the number of guests is already amazing these days, isn't it?
Yes, we have 20 guests today. Today we have 20 guests.
We have a record number of guests this time as well. It's okay because it's Yoshi-san.
That's right.
We have a lot of guests.
We have a huge number of guests, as many as we have in a big special program.
This time, too, we have divided the program into three parts, and we have invited a total of 20 guests.
Let's get started.
So let's get started.
Let's start talking about it.
Let's get started.
Some of the guests.
Some guests.
No, no, no, I'm not going. At the start.
The tone of the people is beautiful, and they're all in one voice.
So it would be better to go around there.
And, you know what? The screen is a little darker than the raw brightness.
It's usually the opposite. It's usually the opposite.
It's really bright here. The screen is dark.
Normally, you have to make the screen look brighter. It's more realistic than the real scene.
It's the opposite.
Why is that?
It's stylish.
No, but it's a little...
It's like Terra South.
It's stylish in terms of atmosphere.
It's in the picture quality, though.
Yes, it is.
Okay, let's go to some of our guests.
I'm Uka and this is Mr. Ameflash. Please give them my best regards.
Oh!
Thank you very much.
Both of you have been here a couple of times already.
That's right.
You two have been here a couple of times.
Yes, they have. Yes, they have.
How about these two couples together? This is the first time.
Until now, you picked up one couple and talked with them, didn't you?
Yes, that's right.
Now, we are just gathering a bunch of people.
The number is increasing.
Have the two groups you've done so far ever worked together?
We have the same office.
You have the same office.
No, we don't have the same office.
No?
But we don't have much contact with each other as a group.
That's right.
Even when we are together, we don't get along very well.
I see.Heh.
Doesn't that mean they don't get along?
Stop it.
You don't get along?
Well, we don't get along.
Distance?
I thought we were pretty good friends.
So that's how it is.
Oh, so you're working together.
Which one of you is the senior?
I don't know.
Probably,
I think we formed this way.
In terms of age, there are many older children.
Yes, there are.
Then we are about the same age now.
I'll give you my profile again.
Today, I'm going to ask you to get to know each other.
Please do.
Please get along with me.
I don't think so. This is the way it's going to go.
Ukkasan.
2019 First Hall Concert,
Clarification from Sakura Evies,
major debut in 2022.
Sakura Evies?
Heh.
Sounds like such a comedic duo.
Even if they are a comedian duo, the name of the duo is very appropriate, isn't it?
They were the Sakura Evades.
They were the Sakura Ebbies.
We were lucky. They changed their name.
Ukka of Ukka is cool. That's why.
You changed it a lot. Sakura Evies.
What did you mean by that? Sakura Eeze.
Sakura Evades became Ukka.
Yes.
That's great.
The name of the group was already decided,
We were recruiting. The audition.
Sakura Ebbies.
Oh, so you all applied to become Sakura Ebbies.
That's right.
Sakura Ebbies.
The sister of Ebi Junior High School.
Ebbies of the flow of Ebi Junior High School.
Tinier than shrimp, Sakura Ebiizu.
I see.
It's totally different from Private Ebi Junior High School, isn't it? Sakura Ebiizu.
Eunance is.
So, next is Ukka.
Yes.
Yes. You made a bold change, didn't you?
That's right.
I see. Well, let's start over,
In addition to their solid singing ability and musicality, they are developing their own unique collaborative activities,
We are a six-member vocal and dance group.
Thank you all for coming today.
Thank you very much.
Next, let's go to AmeFlash.
Formed in November 2018, she said,
They are a fusion of girl crush like K-pop group and Japanese style idol.
The atmosphere is different.
They are an idol group with a unique presence with their dedicated dance performance, vocals, visuals, and artwork.
So, could you introduce yourselves?
Yes. Once again.
Let's start with Uka-san.
Good evening, everyone. We are Uka.
Yes, I'm Me Kawasaki.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I'm Murahoshi Suizumi, nice to meet you.
Yes, I am Akane Developer Screw. Yes, I'm Akane Developer Screw, nice to meet you.
Yes, I am Mizusawa Moa, nice to meet you.
Yes, I am Yukina, nice to meet you. Yes, I am Yukirina, nice to meet you.
Yes, I am AoiNor, the temporary drawing version.
Yes, continued, I am The Lovely Float Flash.
Yes, I'm mg.
Yes, I am Hana Kojima. Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, I am Hana Kojima. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I am Ichikou Mezuki. Pleased to meet you.Yes, my name is Mezuki Ichikou. I look forward to working with you.
I'm Megetsu Ichikou, and it's a pleasure to meet you.
This is the Talkin' Leap section, where we will further explore the charms of the members here.
Yes, I'm Mezuki Ichikou,
What? Ira, some fan gave it to you.
Suddenly.
A cup came in.
It's amazing.
What's wrong?
Can't you see it?
Yes, we are releasing a mini-album on May 16.
We are going to release it,
We're going to release it, and we're doing a lot of releases in various places right now,
We are going to have our customers take pictures of us and we are going to spread the word about it,
The videos that our customers posted on TikTok are getting a lot of buzz,
What?
Why? What kind of video?
This is a video of us performing a song before the show,
The song is the one that they are going to play before the show,
And when they came on stage, they danced to a song called "Zatto Zatto" to make the show more exciting.
The audience took a video of us dancing to a song called "Zatto Zatto" to get everyone excited.
The audience took a video of us dancing to a song called "Zatzatzatzatz" and uploaded it to TikTok,
Aira is getting a lot of buzz right now.
What?
Can I see it?
No, you can't.
You can't?
You can't see it.
No, you can't.
Yes, that's good.
I wanted it. You can see it.
You forced me to screw it up.
I can't read this.
He said he was doing it.
I'm reconsidering the next course.
If you read it,
I'll just have to backtrack and get the explanation.
Then I don't need it.
Oh, but something just came in.
What?
You can see it?
I can't see it.
What are you doing here?
I don't know. I'm just trying to explain.
I don't know... he brought his iPad like he was a manager.
Maybe that's our comment.
Is that what this is about?
Is that a comment?
I'll get it later.
I see. An iPad that accepts comments.
Well then, please check this out.
I'm curious.
I'm curious. I'm curious.
What kind of buzz is that? Is it a great video?
It's some kind of video of me dancing my ass off.
Wow. That's why it's getting buzz?
It's getting around because it's an amazing dance video.
I see. I see.
Please take a look if you like.
Okay.
Okay, let's go. Talkin' Leap Corner. The theme is here.
Here we go.
I've already had this group come a couple of times.
Ha-ha-ha.
Well, those of you who don't know yet.
Well, here is the first one.
Surprisingly, she is a bit of a tearjerker. Who is this?
Yes, I'm Ichikawa.
Oh, Mr. Ichikawa.
That's right. I'm a kind of a solo character in the group,
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, surprisingly, I'm quite refreshing, and I almost never show tears at live performances.
Oh, I don't cry that much at live performances. I don't cry that much at live performances.
I mean, does everyone cry except you? At live performances.
I cry a lot. It's awful. Yamazawa-san.
Oh, my God.
It's been a long time since I've seen him cry.It's been a while since I left, before that.
What's "do-hi-dee"?
Duh-doh-doh. So, when do people cry, for example?
No, it's really a live performance,
I'm happy that so many people came to the show.
I sometimes cry when I hear the audience's final thoughts.
Ah, tears of gratitude from idols.
Do you ever cry?
No, I don't.
It's better to cry, wow, cry, and say thank you.
I like Trice too, but I cry every time.
During the performance.
I think it's okay to cry, but I can't talk because I'm crying so much,
I mean, the chains get really long and push and stuff.
No, no, no, that's fine.
Don't talk about that kind of thing.
He told me that the other three were crying a lot,
I said, "I'm going to push you, so please don't cry too much.
I said, "I want you to cry.
So I would breathe in so much that blood would come out.
So why did you cry when you fell so hard? At that time.
What kind of tears? What made you happy?
I guess the final show of the tour,
Did you remember many things?
Or, did you have some regrets?
Bugs, bugs, bugs!
Big bugs!
It's getting hot in here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Not at all. Not at all.
I've never seen anything like this.
At the end of the tour, there were times when I was happy, but there were also times when I was frustrated.
Frustrating? What?
Like you couldn't fill the capacity.
It's so real.
Oh no, that's a lot of tears.
Maybe I ate a little too much food at the finals. Oh, I see.
Those are really honest tears.
I had a lot of feelings, unexpectedly.
It's been quite a long time, so a lot of feelings came pouring out.
But, you know, I have a solo concert in the summer, and I'm pretty sure it will draw 10,000 people.
Wow! That's a bold move, this year.
To be honest, I don't think we'll be able to fill it. Let's cry if it doesn't fill up, you know.
That's it, bugs, bugs, bugs! Bugs are born bugs.
Ignore it.
Just ignore it.
But, you know, for the customers who paid to see the show, isn't it strange to hear them crying that there are empty seats? That situation.
It makes the customers want to do their best, too.
They want to support us.
We didn't want them to feel that way on the next tour.
I see. You cried so much that you had to push the audience a little bit?
No, there are writers and MC's in front of me, but I've been in the front row for a long time,
But I was at the very front, like this, all the time.
Even though you are crying?
How can you do that? I did this to a crying girl.
Is that why you cry so often?
No, because they come to me.
Oh, cut it out.
It's coming to me.
Ichikawa-san is the only one who is sober now.
Aira, cut out your tears and hurry up and move on to the next one.
That's too much.
That's great.
You always do such a great job.
I see.
I don't cry much.
Yes, I do. I'm surprisingly tearful, but that's the theme.
That's true.
Why do you cry a lot?
I have a weakness for emotional things, and if there is a movie or an animated cartoon or something like that, I cry easily.
Oh, I see.
When you fly on an airplane, you can watch a movie.
I was sitting next to someone and I thought it was noisy, but it was a big high-class movie,
I was crying on the plane, and I wondered what I was doing.
I can cry on airplanes.
No, I'm so emotionally involved.
Oh, so you can cry a lot in your work.
That's right.
Yeah, but it doesn't hit me at all in that one of the customers.Oh, but I won't hit at all with that one of the customers.
No, no, no, it's not a good idol.
Idol is a blur.
No, no, no. That's why you're the type to cry properly.
Oh, I see. Don't misunderstand me.
Yes, please don't misunderstand me.
I see.
Shall we go next? Okay, then. Next, this way.
Yes.
I'm confident in my 00. Who is this?
Yes, this is Akane Sora. This is Akane Sora.
Yes, this is Sora Akane. Sora Akane.
I have confidence in my fans.
You have confidence in your fans?
Yes, I am. Well, the last time I came here, I was told that I probably scrubbed the screenshots of the fans' talk pages and so on,
I am very good at remembering my fans,
I am very good at remembering my fans.
That's a good thing.
It's not pressure.
But if you look at some of the comments, you'll see what I mean,
I get a lot of comments from fans.
They say, "You remember so well.
Oh, I see.
I'd like to say more like, "Do you remember? And you don't feel comfortable saying that you don't remember?
I don't.
You don't? Because you remember?
Because I'm sure I remember.
You're sure you remember?
Yes, I'm sure.
Wow, I hated it so much. I used to hate it.
Do you understand? I know.
I used to get quizzed about my name.
That happened in the past.
I didn't tell you my name, did I?
It's nice to be told, "Oh, wow! It's nice to be told "Oh, wow!
But the pressure of being asked.
I'll get over it.
Oh, but you still have it, don't you?
You are good at it.
Yes, I am.
You can remember.
I can remember people's names, too.
But my college friends...
I can't remember the names of my fans,
But I can remember the names of Marumaru's friends.
I see.
I see. So I don't have to remember any names?
You are the one from that time, right?
No, I'll tell you his name.
You'll tell me his name, too?
I'll tell you what happened, where we met, and so on.
Oh, you are MARUMARU, right?
Yes, I still remember.
It's nice to be used by fans.
I am very good at that,
I often introduce my fans to my friends.
What? Friends?
Yes, that's right.
What's that?
That's so cute.
Maybe you shouldn't do that.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
What do you mean?
The test?
Are you okay?
Usually, I talk about it when I'm with my friends,
I was talking to this fan the other day,
I was talking about this fan who's going abroad.
Or something,
Oh, so that's what it's about.
Insects!
It's an insect.
No, don't worry about what I said.
So, you know, when we take a group photo or something,
I'm looking at his face,
I'd look at his face and say, "What do you think he does?
I'd quiz him.
No, it's tough.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's a bug.It's a bug.
It's a bug.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ah, there it is.
There it is. There it is.
They think your head is a nest.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, it's almost embedded.
It was stuck.
It stopped.
Oh, no, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha.
Let's stop.
Let's stop messing around with bugs.
Huh? It's stopping now.
It's stopped, but it's making me cry
Let's not make a fuss about bugs.
Let's go next time.
No, I'm curious.
Oh, I'm stopping.
I'm going to die! I'm running out of steam.
I'm sure you're right.
Oh, this is like a paper cup...
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Is there anything like that?
It's not like that...
Well, well, well...
I see.
That's great... but that's the customer, isn't it?
Let's continue.
How do you interact with seniors?
That's me. We Stardust idols get together and have festivals and stuff.
I'm also in a group with Airin from Momokuro.
We're planning to go to Disney next time.
But I get nervous in private.
I can't talk well.
Oh, I see.
I think comedians have a hierarchical relationship,
How do you get along with your seniors?
Oh, yes, that's true.
What is the hierarchical relationship like for idols?
Are they like friends?
But I don't know, studer, I mean, I'm a stapler, but...
I've met a lot of adult astriders, even senior ones, who are very friendly and talk to me,
I think it's because many of the adult astriders, even the older ones, are very friendly and talk to the younger ones,
I don't feel like there is a strict hierarchical relationship outside,
I don't feel like there's a strict hierarchical relationship outside.
Ah....
Everyone is so nice.
Do you want to eat? Dinner.
What are we gonna do when we get there? Who's gonna fix it?
No, we'll go.
I've never been.
What?
I don't know, I've just...
You don't like me.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I see.
No, I think that maybe if I invited you, you would go,
But we've been working as sister groups,
I don't think we can go in there on our own.
That's right.
I see.
But, I see. So you don't even get invited? Not really.
No, but we do make verbal promises.
Like, "Let's go out to dinner sometime.
Ah, I see.
I see. So it's not like comedians, where you get together at a concert or something,
So it's not like you get together at a concert and go out for dinner afterwards? No.
Even if you get together with a few groups at a festival, do they all go home?
That's right. It doesn't seem like there is usually a place to eat nearby, does it?
I have an image of them doing it someplace a bit far away.
Really? That's why the members are so close to each other, in an idol way. That's true.
That's true. Who do you often hang out with? Do you go out for dinner or hang out?
Certainly. Members?Certainly. Member?
I'm still a member of Amegras.
I don't care about American Glass anymore, do I? Friends? Friends. That's right.
I'm too shy.
Friends with different idols. I see. But why don't you invite them?
If it's 4, I'll go to a drinking party with Mr. Imada or something next time.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
And maybe Mr. Umakano.
I like that. I like it. Sounds fun.
Don't you want to go? I don't want to go.
I don't want to go.
I want to go.
Mr. Imada's drinking party.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's so graphic.
What do you mean by "graphic"?
It doesn't matter. As a junior, he asked me to teach him about hierarchical relationships.
As a kid who came to learn about hierarchical relationships.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Mr. Imada, drinking party.
But it's good. But I think it's nice.
I'm going to Disney next time. That sounds nice.
It is. We've already decided on a date.
Oh, it's decided.
Yes, I have. So, what are we going to do then?
With Ernie?
Yes. What are we going to dress up as?
How many of you are there?
Eight.
That's great. It's like everyone is dressing up.
They wear catsuits, and everyone says, "Let's do that.
Are they all idols?
We were in a group called Namie Girls' First Name.
Oh, I see. So it's almost like it's a job.
No, no, no, no, no.
Look at this.
But when people think you're nervous or oblivious, they invite you to join.
Especially me.
I see.
Shimada also invites me out. I guess so.
He doesn't seem nervous.
I think he relaxes. I think they are more likely to ask me out if they feel like they are having fun,
I think they're more likely to ask me out.
I see.
I learned a lot from this.
Thank you very much.
Next, this way.
Yes, there are more things I can eat. Kawase?
Yes, it's Kawase.
What's this? There are more and more things we can eat. Seriously, you don't have anything to say?
I didn't have much to say. This is the third time we've met.
I have so many likes and dislikes about food that I can't even keep track of them.
There are so many things I don't like. Oh, that's about it. Simple.
Simple.
Simple. Today's person really wants to eat all the things they don't like.
They eat it, though,
Something of that,
Recently, the number of things I can eat has been increasing,
For example,
For example, he can eat strawberries,
but he can't eat anything strawberry-flavored.
Ah~~.
That's right.
Strawberry Pocky?
Ah~~.
Strawberry Pocky...
No, I don't get it at all.
Hmmm...
Melon is good, but..,
But something with melon flavor,
You know how you like melon, but you don't like melon-flavored something or other? Like watermelon.
It's too sweet for you. Oh.
Too sweet for you? Yes.
Or strawberry-flavored something. Or strawberry-flavored something.
Or ice cream? Yes.
Strawberry ice cream? Vanilla ice cream? Yes.
Heh. It tastes like it was made.
Uh... Vanilla flavor.
Ah, I know.Oh, I know.
That wasn't there, but that time I ate a strawberry-flavored chocolate ball.
Yes, I could still eat it.
I could still eat them, and I was worried that I might be able to eat them.
I was worried that I could eat it.
And now that I'm 21 years old, I'm getting more and more.
What's that?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Grown-up ghost stories.
What else can you eat?
I can eat avocado now.
Oh, wow.
It's coming out.
It's out.
Oh, no.
I still can't eat it.
Well, a lot of whipped cream.
A lot? Don't put "a lot" on it.
I can't have a lot of chili either.
If it's something like that, don't put a lot of it.
If it's a cake, it's got to be a lot.
Even shortcake. You can eat shortcake? Yes, I can.
Oh, I see. Wow.
It's in large quantities. Wow. So you can eat it with whipped cream?
It's good if it has a whipped cream accent.
Like a custard of whipped cream, a little bit of whipped cream, and some cream puffs.
Ah. Ahh.
I can eat custard cream. Tube cream is edible.
Yes.
It's all pretty sweet, isn't it?
What else?
Mushrooms.
All of them?
All of them.
Wow.
Maitake and all?
Enoki mushrooms, shimeji mushrooms.
Enoki mushrooms are good.
Wow.
Oh, there are a lot of them.
I don't know, but..,
Some people don't like mushrooms.
I don't know, I don't like them myself.
Ah.
Commonalities.
You're all over the place.
Yeah.
Huh.
I can't drink soda.
I see. You've got a sensitive mouth, huh? It's delicate. It makes my throat go "ahhh".
You don't get sick of whipped cream? Oh, yeah. Yes, it is. Yes, I do.
And the rest? All jellied? Paprika. Paprika. That's a dead end.
You don't drink? I don't drink soda, so I can't have sours or beer.
Are you okay with alcohol? Yeah, I'm fine.
Huh. What about salty food? Sashimi, fish?
How about fish, like salmon or squid?
I can't eat fish, salmon roe, etc.
You can't eat them? I can't eat them. I don't like the fishy smell.
Tuna?
What?
Interesting. Grilled white meat.
I'd like to use scallops, too,
No other shellfish.
What?
Interesting.
No, you can probably eat all of them.
I'm serious.
What?
I'm sure you can.
It's tough.
My girlfriend is like this.
It's really tough.
It's fun, but it's not really irresistible.
I'm really popular.
But I think my friends and I ate dinner together,
I'll decide. I decide where to eat.
Oh, I see.
Oh, no.
It's too hard.
Yes, but...Yes, but...
What was kind?
No, no, no.
When the job was done and I couldn't make it,
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't be able to eat what I want.
I had no money.
You have to go.
What the hell?
It's tough.
Oh, yeah.
Let's advertise this gradually.
Yes, that's right. I want to advertise it.
But there are moments when you know you've made it, right?
Choco Balls, for example.
That's right.
I think we'll be able to go on from here.
I'd love to see you at Japan Kubi.
That's for sure.
You know, the ones that are lined up in a row.
What?
I don't like it.
All of them.
Oh.
That's a lot of money.
What? That story.
I talked like a dream.
Now, let's continue.
Yes, sir.
Is it coming out? - No.
No, I haven't had juice in three years. What is this?
Yes, I'm Miki Murahoshi.
Yes, oh.
As the name says, I drank juice for the first time in three years.
What is this? Why?
Why did you drink it for 3 years?
Let me tell you why I did not drink it,
I myself can live my life with water and tea.
I can live with water and tea.
But that doesn't mean I can't drink juice because I don't like it,
But it's not that I can't drink juice because I don't like it, but because I can't drink juice, such as orange juice or apple juice,
I can taste the juice, for example, orange juice or apple juice, and I can feel that it tastes good,
But I don't voluntarily want to drink orange juice,
It's delicious.
I haven't had orange juice in a while.
But don't they have juice, tea, and water on site?
Yes, there are.
Do you still choose water or tea?
Oh, yes. First, you bring water from home.
I see.
You are drinking water.
It's good for the hips, the body. A little bit of head.
It's great.
I can't drink much cola.
I can't drink cola or anything like that.
I can't really drink anything that tastes sweet.
Last October, I turned 20 years old, and about 7 months later, I haven't had a drop of alcohol.
You don't even want to drink?
I don't want to drink. I don't want to drink, but I don't really want to drink.
I'm keeping a record of how much I don't drink.
I know I'm in that zone, but that's not why I'm doing it.
Coffee?
I can't drink coffee.
Even if you go to a drink bar?
I don't drink.
So it's either a drink bar or a soft drink bar.
Comment] It is good when you choose a soft drink or drink oolong tea, isn't it?
But, you know, I still can't drink it, so...
Oh!
What a waste, then.
Soft drink or drink bar
What do you like? Okay, bye.
I don't mind if we go out to eat or something.
Uh...
Dinner?
I'd also like to have a snack.
Okay.
What do you like?
Bread is my favorite.
Ha-ha-ha.
I don't like to drink juice.
Ha-ha-ha.Ha-ha-ha.
With a little tea drinking.
Crunchy bread?
Oh, yeah.
That's why my parents and others
They wonder why I can go for water and bread. How can you have water and bread? Like, "How can you have water and bread?
Since you were a child?
Since I was a child, well, since I was a child,
I had a lot of likes and dislikes,
I drank a little bit of orange juice, but that was it.
I drank mostly barley tea.
I also like the taste. I like the taste of this.
I've been drinking it for about three years.
Yes, I've been drinking it for about three years.
I thought it was orange juice. Ah, that's why it doesn't move you,
I guess so. I was like, "Oh, yeah, this is what it tastes like.
Oh, yeah, it tastes like this. Yes.
But it's good, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's kind of good, isn't it? Yeah, it's good.
I'm jealous. I'm okay with it, too.
It looks like it's good for you. It's true.
I don't drink, and I have this image that it has some kind of coloring or something on it. Oh, I don't know.
Do you eat vegetables? Oh, I like vegetables.
Oh, that's good. That's good.
It's healthy. That's good.
Oh. Do you drink juice or alcohol?
I drink, but juice, sure, but I kind of get it.
Juice is such a...
So, you know, you go into a convenience store and you want to drink something juice-y,
And sometimes I don't even want one.
Ah.
I don't want something just the right size, and I don't want Coke 500 anymore.
I just can't find anything that's good for me.
Maybe vegetable juice.
That's for sure.
The convenience store used to look so bright and shiny.
That's why the amount of Red Bull is the best.
Ah.
I can see why.
Sure.
Health-conscious.
Yeah.
As for alcohol, well, I don't drink sweets anymore,
More and more.
I used to be able to drink a lot of juice-like drinks.
I don't need much. I want them to drink alcohol, though.
Why not?
If you drink alcohol, if you can drink alcohol, then, you know, what is it?
Not a sour or something, but, you know, water.
Or shochu.
Wow.
That's cool.
Shochu?
Cool.
Wow.
That's all there is.
Plum wine is probably no good.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't like anything that's too juice-like.
Oh, I see.
Then maybe it's that way.
It's uncharted territory.
That's interesting.
Yeah, it is.
It would be fun to get hooked on alcohol.
Ha-ha-ha.
Under the circumstances.
Now, then, here we go.
Yes.
You can do any imitation.
This is...
Who is this?
Yes, I'm Hana Kojima.
Did you get it?
I did.
Ha-ha-ha.
Kojima-san.
What?Huh?
What are you talking about, having them come here.
I want to do the moniker over and over again.
Did you do that one yet?
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm still working on it.
What?
You can do any imitation.
Yes, I can.
Well, you know, it's not that we look so much alike, but...
Let's stop, then.
Ha-ha-ha.
I can imitate anything, so I would love to do it if you make a request.
Requests?
No, I mean, that's why you've been doing it on social networking sites.
Yes, that's right.
What?
What do you mean by this request?
You mean here, now?
Yes.
Is that okay?
Well, I mean, can I just talk?
I'm not very good at doing impersonations of, you know, this person or that person,
For example..,
No people.
What do you call it, someone who stepped on your pinky finger?
I'm not very good at impersonating people who have had their pinky stepped on. I'm not very good at that.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...,
I usually find someone who is in vogue right now.
Yes, but my impersonation.
I'm not going to do that.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, I won't.
They'll say, "You're a comedian," or "Nishiki goi-san," or something.
Oh, no, I don't mean that.
Sei-chan, is that good?
Ouch.
But say something. I'm going to imitate someone who is in real pain from being stepped on by a little finger, but is holding it in.
You were dressed so erotically, there.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're fashionable. Sexy and fashionable.
Okay, I'll leave you to it.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Stop it, stop it.
Laugh.
Laughing.
That hurts so much.
It's a really long scale.
LOL.
How cleanly you do something like that.
I can do it. No way, it's a long version.
LOL.
It's rare to see such a long version.
It's good to see it after a long time.
Fujima's impersonation.
It's rare.
I am good at imitating people.
Then, I can imitate someone who came to the airport and didn't have a passport.
I understand.
So, here it is. Finally, it was right where I said it was.
Oh, it's good! Yum!
So it's good, huh? So we just have to decide where to end it.
Wow.
Oh, I see.
Is that okay with you?
I don't know... I'm just an imitator whose skills are not similar to yours.
No way. Why, why, why? Imitating people whose skills are not similar to mine.
Last time I gave something to Yakko-san,
Would you like to have a showdown with Hana-chan?
A showdown?
I don't care if it's a corocoro or anything else.
Oh, no, no, no. Really?
Then, let's do it together.
Sure.
Two people who say it's okay to step on each other's feet,
We'll have a quick match.
Oh, I see.Oh, I see.
The one with the footsteps, flying...
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, then.
Okay. Yeah.
Train by train by train
Train rattling, train shaking.
Let me fly.
Train, yeah.
Train, ambulance.
Kojima-san says he's fine, but
But Muraguchi's out of it.
You're the one who said we should definitely go to the hospital.
Yes, an ambulance.
Okay, please.
Sorry, sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
In the world for sure... Definitely not. w
I can't think. rate
LOL!
I really....
I can't believe it's settled.
OK!
OK! Okay!
There you go!
Elephant.
Yeah! Two guys who can do it! Who else?
Laughter.
No contest!
You're gonna get it!
This is not gonna happen!
This will never happen!
You're the fairy that breeds shitty actors.
LOL!
You're copying from somewhere. This.
laughter
I don't think it's the look.
No, it's nice.
That's followed by this one.
Everything positive.
What is this?
Who is this?
Yes! It's Selizamar.
Mr. Selizer.
What's this?
Well, I'm not sure...
I make a lot of mistakes with each other.
I've been doing it so much that I've started to think positively about everything.
Oh, I see.
I see.
So, what about something that happened at home recently?
Oh, this? If you have something like that, I'll turn it into something positive,
I'll turn it into something positive, so please let me know.
What? I felt it was negative.
- Yes, I did. I'd appreciate it. Lately,
Oh, well, you're going to have to work a little harder today,
I was going to do some muscle training today, but..,
But then I just slack off in my room.
Oh well.
Well, that happens every day.
But when I do that, I consider it a learning experience.
Learned?
I basically go in and say, "I learned something,
Today, for example,
I learned something. I learned something,
Then, I'll get up a little earlier tomorrow,
I will learn something, and I will be calm,
I can make myself calm. To be calm,
Yes.
I didn't take a cab today,
What about when you're late for a meeting?
Well, I'm learning...
Ha-ha-ha.
That's enough.
That's what everyone thinks.
It's a learning experience.
We're aware of that before you are.
You're learning...
That's what life is all about, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha.
You shouldn't say that to older people.You can't say that to older people.
They all know.
I'm glad you're learning. Um...
No, I'll use the bike.
No, no, no, it's a learning experience.
That's what I'm trying to say, that everything is a learning experience, even the things you don't like.
You learn from them.
You're learning.
That's why you're learning.
What's the real point?
Can I ask you to study Japanese?
I'd like you to learn.
Please study.
And now, this way, please.
Step forward.
Who is this?
Yes, that's me.
I am.
Well...
Well, I look like this, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
Well, I was the chairman of the committee in junior high school.
Chairperson?
Committee chairman?
Chair of the committee.
What? Committee chair? Now.
The girl from the committee?
Committee girl.
What? Chairwoman?
Committee... committee...
Oh, committee chair... committee chair?
Oh...
The girl from the committee is called "chairperson"?
Yes, I think so.
Committee chair is a school...
No, no, I was the chair of the environmental committee.
I'm sorry, I don't understand so far.
Chairperson.
Um, cleaning and stuff.
You're talking fast.
I'm just talking, so wait a minute.
Sorry, sorry.
Chairman of the Environment Committee.
That's right.
As the chairperson, you have a lot of opportunities to speak in front of people.
When you do that, you tend to talk too fast, or your face turns red.
That's exactly what I'm doing now.
My ears are all over the place.
My face is red and my mouth is almost closed when I speak.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm working, so I'm still clean,
I want to become a woman who can speak properly,
I wondered what I should do.
Well, you know, I've been doing that at gigs, and I'm doing it today, too,
You talk a lot, don't you?
Yes.
So, do you think it will gradually get better?
Your rapid speech seems to be increasing.
Oh, I see.
I see.
You are not good at public speaking? In front of people like that?
I like it, but I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at speaking.
I can sing and dance live, but not at all.
I like to sing and dance live, but I also like to talk,
I went to a fortune teller the other day, and she told me that if I talk too much, I'll come off as a complete idiot,
So, I think it's better for me not to talk.
Maybe I'm more suited to a quiet, stoner-like demeanor.
Ahh...
I'm starting to wonder which type I am.
Which way does he want to go? He wants to talk.
Well, I think it's better to let myself go, so I'll have an impromptu session with Kojima-san here,
If I improvise with Mr. Kojima here once, I might be able to free myself.
Well, but that's what I call getting used to it.
But that's what makes you a character, isn't it?
Nervous.
I'm going to be a character with red ears.
I mean, I'm not sure if I'm going to have red ears.
I'm embarrassed.
But it's a good character, kind of, you know, nice.But a nice character, kind of, you know, nice.
He talks a little too fast,
I mean, it's like a good character.
In a good way, in a good way, of course.
But as a character, of course.
There are a lot of people who like that kind of person.
You like him?
Huh? Hmm?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
People like that?
Oh, like me.
No, I don't really like them.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You don't?
Yes, I do.
But I don't know.
Maybe I like it.
I think I like her a little less than being imposing.
Well, she's cute.
I think it's good.
Thank you.
Let's continue.
Next, here we go.
We're looking for a property.
Hey, hey, hey.
Too much nothing.
Woman.
Who's this?
I'm sorry. I'm Ira.
Oh, it's Ira.
Ira, what is it?
I've been thinking about living on my own,
I'm really enjoying looking at properties.
Oh, yes.
I mean, a 5,000-yen increase in rent can really make a difference in where you can live, can't it?
So I took pictures of properties and watched movies.
- And I enjoy watching movies and so on. It's fun. Well, it is fun, isn't it?
And sometimes, when I see something that looks like an orb..,
I'm off! Maybe I'm stuck inside! I'm scared! I'm scared!
- I'm scared. I'm looking at it a lot.
- I wonder what life would be like if we lived there,
I'm wondering if there's anything I can do to help.
What's that? Are you looking for one town in particular?
Or are you looking in many places?
I'm looking for a lot of things.
Wow.
In my job, I look for places that are very far from the office,
I also look for places that are very close to the office.
Ah.
I guess only rich people can live in this area.
Do you also check rents that you would never live in?
I also look into places like Roppongi.
Roppongi is expensive.
Ah. Properties.
I love looking at that kind of thing, too,
I love looking at those kinds of places, but I can't help thinking about what the two of you would not compromise on.
Why do you want to hear that?
Ha-ha-ha.
You guys are too random!
I'm not going.
What the hell is that?
I'm sure you'll squeeze it out of him.
I have a point.
What about you, Aira?
I definitely have separate bathrooms and toilets.
What? You're just a normal person.
Also, you know what else?
It should face south.
Sunshine?
Sunshine.
A lot of women value sunlight.
I think it'll stand out against the light fixtures.
Oh, that way?
Ha-ha-ha.
I don't know if it's that way or if it's dark at night.
That way. That way.
Is there something there?
There's something I can't give up.
I'll give it up. After all, why should I give it all up?I'll give it away. After all, why give it all away?
But now, I'd prefer to have separate bathrooms and toilets.
That's right.
They used to be the same.
Bathroom.
They used to be so much the same.
Yes, we did.
We were together just the other day.
Yeah.
Until a year and a half ago, we were already spending 56,000 yen.
Wow.
But you don't want to do that anymore, right?
Yes, that's true. It's much more comfortable with a little more space.
Heh.
You get used to it, don't you?
That's right. That's why we stayed at a hotel the other night.
We are used to staying in separate rooms, so hotels are the same.
Even if you close the curtains and take a bath,
I noticed that the toilet was all wet.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
It was already flowing through the cracks.
They are not used to it. I'm not used to this way of doing things.
But that's my point.
I can't compromise on that,
I don't like the fact that it takes so long to get to the elevator.
Ah.
You know, there are times when I want to poop myself from the entrance of a man-centered apartment building.
Just before I leave. Ah, I see.
At that time, I thought that the length of the room would be quite hard for me. That's true.
And then, for a moment at home, I thought, wow, I forgot my cell phone,
I don't like to go back home to get my cell phone, so I was surprised,
It's just a moment. So it's easy.
That's easy. But, you know, there is no proper security. Well, you know.
That's right. That's right.
Yeah. On the contrary, I only gave up my auto-lock.
What?
I don't like auto locks.
Really?
Are you afraid of them?
That's what's important, isn't it?
Women say "auto-lock", right?
That's true.
Well, well, the location.
What is the best place to live?
Is there a place that is the best place to live?
I don't know, this area.
No, but I'll live in the place I just recommended.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'll tell them.
I'll live where I just recommended.
Idols don't really know where they live.
What are you looking at? Well, aside from whether they live there or not.
Which part makes you excited? Right now.
Oh, you mean the tension right now?
I'm thinking of Shibuya,
Or Shimokitazawa.
Wow.
Not at all, but Shibuya.
I like the ocean.
I like Enoshima...
Well, that's...
That's...
That's... I mean, you know...
Huh?
Enoshima's Second Life.
Oh.
I can't live in Enoshima.
I want to live there when I get settled.
I see.
Ah, that's nice.
I can dream about a place on Enoshima.
That's true. I don't know much about that place over there, Toyosu and so on.
Hmmm.
I don't know much about that place, but Toyosu...well, it's a reclaimed land.
That's for sure.
Over there, like Shibaura, over there.
Hmmm.
It's high.
Yes, it is.
Carman over there.
It's expensive. It's expensive.It's expensive. It's expensive.
Well, I'm working on another project called Admission Real Estate, so Rabbit. Rabbit.
Oh, I saw it. I saw it.
You haven't introduced any girls yet.
We could really go there. There. What?
I want to move there. My first idol.
By all means. By all means.
I've never seen an idol searching for a place on TV.
Ha-ha-ha. Surely. Definitely.
Definitely. Absolutely. It was fun.
Thank you very much. And now, on to the last one.
This way.
Yes, choose your guess. Now, who is this?
Yes, this is Yukirina. This is our third time to perform in hookah,
This is also the third time with Inokyu.
I assume that you know hookah to some extent,
Then, I thought that you must have a preference among the six of us,
I would like to ask them who they prefer among the six of them.
I am very conscious of this.
That's right. It could get a little sticky after this.
What do you think?
Who is it?
I'll be here for three days.
You're all cute. They're really cute.
They're all cute. They really are.
That means they're not here.
They're all really cute. Everyone is cute.
Then it's no good.
It's no good.
Who do you want?
I'm Aiji, right?
No, you're not.
Different group.
We'll do it in Ukka.
No, no.
Gross.
This is not at all.
Don't do it in Ukka.
What is the most really important?
The actress you like.
You're aiming a little bit.
Can I ask you to stop for a second?
Can I ask you to stop?
I like everyone.
If I have to choose because I like them.
No, but, you know, the characters, they're all very strong characters.
No, but everyone, eh? Based on what?
No, Ira, if you're so decisive...
You have to decide so much?
And vodka.
No, Ira.
Ira, you're the best of the best.
Ukka, isn't she one of them?
I'm too early.
I'm sure she's great.
What? Ukka?
Ira, I know you're good with the vodka, vodka, vodka, vodka.
But you know what?
You're good characters, all of you.
But, Moa...
What's with the vibe?
I really don't like it. I don't like this.
I think this is the most stupid time.
I don't know who we like.
That's what you said.
Everyone is fine, though.
I see.
How about you, Hiro?
I'm...
I'm sorry, I can't tell you. I have a wife.
It's great, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great.
You didn't just say that?
Shh.
Whew.
I'm sorry. I have a wife.
I can't tell you.
Shh.
Shhh.
Archives
Please take another look at the archives.Take another look in the archives.
Well, that's it.
So that's it.
That's it.
Now then, we have an announcement.
Ladies and gentlemen...
We're releasing our first major single on June 21st.
For real? First? Major first?
Yes, I'm serious. Before that, we released our major first mini-album last year.
Oh, I see.
This is the first time we are releasing a single.
That's great!
Yes, it is. I'm sorry. I'm working on a Lace event right now.
I'm going to be in the Kansai area the day after tomorrow for 8 days.
For real?
Yes, a Lace event.
You're having us do the Kansai 4D?
Yeah.
4D drawing.
So we'd love for you to come visit us.
Oh, okay.
Please do.
What's with all the happiness?
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I won't go first.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm going home.
Turn in.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Seriously, let's go again.
No, it's falling. It's falling.
Come on, let's go.
Can I bring my junior?
Let's all have a drink together.
Don't drink with everyone.
Why not, vodka?
I mean, I'm not gonna have a drink with you guys.
Is that bad?
No?
So you're okay with that?
Yes, I'm fine.
Then I'll have an Ameflavi, please.
Okay.
Yes. We're launching a mini all-around coffee on May 16th.
We're launching a coffee, and with that...
Yes, we are going to have a Billy Bear.
The nearest one is in Fukuoka on May 4.
We will be traveling to Fukuoka on May 4. And the next day is...
On May 5th, I will be at Tower Records Shibuya.
Oh, from Fukuoka?
The next day?
Yes, the next day.
It's a red one in the middle.
Please come. It's an easy event to come to, even for first-timers.
I hope you will come.
Fukuoka on the 7th.
Wow! That's too bad!
Can't you come back on the 4th?
I can't go back on the 4th.
Then we'll go on the 7th.
If you stay until the 7th, let's go out for dinner.
Wow!
He said he'll have more dinner sometime.
I don't understand.
He said we should go out to eat until the 7th.
And the rest?
Yes, here's the rest.
On July 9, at Lenny's in Shinjuku.
I'll be doing a one-man show, Bio-san 2023, at Shinjuku Lenny on July 9.
A one-man show!
Yes!
I know it's winter season and you might be feeling a little down,
But come to this one-man show of Amegrassi,
I hope you will come to this one-man show of Amegrasi and enjoy yourselves,
Tickets are on sale now, so I'll be waiting for you.
Tickets are on sale now, so please wait for them.
So, thank you all very much.
Please come again.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
That's great. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
No, we were in the same office. They're on time, less than a minute apart.
I want those two pairs destroyed at 19:48. Perfect.
That's great. But I'm not so sure about those two groups. That's for sure.
Even if they're in the same office, they probably wouldn't go out to eat.
No, they won't. Afterwards. Maybe after this.
After this? Well, maybe after this.
I don't know why we're not going. What's going on?
I mean, they seem like they'd get along. If they were of the same generation and in the same office.
I guess that's just how idols are. Surprisingly, they are all in the same group and get along well with each other.
Do you think they are enemies?
No, but they really don't get along that seriously, do they? Do you think comedians get together too much?
Yes, indeed. Please have a seat.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
We're getting a lot of comments. I'm going to change the flavor of the second part of the show.
Is that OK? Is that OK? Yes, I'm ready. Okay. Now, the guests for the second part are as follows.
Please give them my best regards. First of all, let's start with Mr. Bradio's new event. Please give my best regards.
Please give my best regards to you. Bradio is a three-piece rock band formed with the concept of "entainment" to add color to everyday life,
The drum bass makes a different sound for each song. Drum bass. Is it called drum bass? Yes.
The band is led by a gokarist, Mr. Shinshigyoji, who has a strong personality and sings in both falsetto and passionate voice,
They are a group of entertainers who make funky party people fall in love with their music. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Next, Mr. Maemura, please.
Yes, please.
Mr. Maemura, please.
Mr. Yoshiaki Maemura.
In addition to his high singing ability, he plays the guitar and talks in a very different style.
In addition, his humor al sampling,
track-making skills.
He is a bright and free-spirited character,
He is a popular storyteller, track maker, and idol.
Thank you very much.
Originally, I was in an idol group,
After the group broke up, I became a singer,
I see. I was an idol...
I grew up in the idol field, so I never forget that.
I see.
There are many reasons.
So you have many reasons.
Thank you very much.
Now, then, Mr. Kazuki Takahashi, please give us your regards.
Please give my best regards.
Mr. Takahashi, armed with a high tone voice that communicates from the heart,
You are a solo singer who mainly performs in logio live concerts.
Yes, I am.
My first album "At Home" was released on July 7,
At Home," which was released on July 7, reached No. 2 on the Oricon Charts.
No. 2?
That's amazing.
Mr. Takahashi visited us before.
He came, he came.
At that time, you were in a group.
That's right, the two of us went to see the show together.
That's right.
And you went to see him live.
What?
This was it.
Yes.
I went to the concert and I loved it.
I mean, I was, you know, with my, you know, partner.
I mean, you know... I've listened to the nonkey she gave me about a hundred times.
Wow.
Well, there were a lot of things that happened.
Yes, I did.
So, how long have you been a solo artist?
Well, since last April.
One year?
Yes, one year has passed.
And you're already in first, oh, second place.
That's amazing.
That's great.That's great.
What, your partner before that already, now?
He is with you, isn't he?
You are together?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm not supposed to mention this.
You can't touch it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, he's got a lot going on, big fight or not.
I don't know if it's a big fight or not, but he's been through a lot.
But he was so tough.
He's amazing in his own way, too. That's exactly what I mean.
He did a lot of things.
I see.
So you are a solo artist now?
Yes, he is.
Oh, wow, there are so many things.
Now, next, let's have the legend of Saitama, Mr. Wanishi. Please give my best regards.
Legend of Saitama, Mr. Wanishi.
Please give my regards to Mr. Wanishi.
Legend of Saitama, Mr. Wanishi, is he, uh, 23, 23 years old?
He is young.
He is young. You can't see.
No, I can't see him anymore.
An all-rounder who can post and back up his videos of shitty, quirky stories.
An influencer who entertains his fans daily with his never-ending stories.
Yes.
Mainly because why, TikTok?
Yes, on TikTok, yes, I was allowed to do, um, father stories.
Dad.
My father.
He's 23 years old.
Dad.
He's 23.
Twenty-three.
So he's not actually your father?
No, he's not. No, he's not.
I don't even have a father.
Uh-huh.
I don't have a father either, but it's really imaginary.
Wow.
That's amazing.
He is fighting, isn't he?
That's really amazing.
I'm curious.
My dad was gone for a long time too.
Oh, really?
I definitely have a father. No, you don't.
Yes, you do.
I picked up some of that stuff from dramas, but I'm more of a comedy person,
If you ask me if it's a perfect example..,
What is it? And then, it became a buzz,
Yes, and then I got an office.
And then you got an office.
Oh, that's right. That's right.
So, at first, you were just a regular guy?
Oh, I was already on my own, yes. Yes.
I mean, that's not how it works. In the case of influencers?
Yes, that's right. Put the camera in a corner of the room,
Okay.
Open the door, what's up? That's how I got the buzz.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm curious to hear what the influencer has to say,
Well, I'd better ask him if I get a hit.
No, you're right.
A trigger.
Well, I should ask.
But that's what you mean, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
That's great.
And so, the speaking jobs started coming up.
Oh, that's right.
You were on the show with Oden, right?
That's right.
With Ueki Oden.
We got a lot of buzz, and we were doing it on that YouTube channel called "Please Tama.
Yeah.Yeah. - Yeah.
I'm a reporter and my sister has a camera.
I mean, we're fighting, and we're in Saitama, Kachok.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's not good.
No, she's already behind the scenes.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
So, you know, there are a lot of things like that.
Yes, there's that connection.
Wow.
Let's hear about it later.
Okay, continue.
Okay.
Mr. Wanted, please.
Mr. Wanted.
What does that mean? We're looking for a name.
I'm looking for a name.
You mean you're actually looking for names?
Keep looking.
Have you been looking for a name for a long time?
About a year.
Wow.
That's great.
You're looking for a name?
Stakas and Ambassadors for 24 hours
with a variety of delicious food content.
He has gained popularity
He is very popular among women for his visual appeal.
influencer.
What are you looking for a name for?
Do you use YouTube?
I mainly use TikTok.
TikTok?
TikTok is the best.
Everyone watches TikTok.
What is it really like to live 24 hours a day?
For example, if you live a 24-hour transparent life...
Oh...
Oh, and eat only agar agar and stuff like that.
Agar agar...
Or water...
And then edit it into a TikTok?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, I see.
Ten hours a week, ten hours a week, that's all you live on.
And practice on it.
Every day.
Every day?
I do something.
You do something every day of your life.
I guess so.
So you're not doing anything today?
I'm doing something today.
What are you doing today?
You don't have to say much.
Today is... Oh, no, no, no.
Today, today, um...
Uh, luxury living.
What?
That's just luxury.
I'm doing so much today.
That's tough, too.
If it costs money...
It's today. Breakfast, lunch...
What did you eat for breakfast, lunch and dinner? What did you eat?
Capias this morning.
Oh, wow!
I see.
It's really tough being an influencer.
Starting in the morning.
That's amazing.
That's funny.
Deep slice.
You can have a deep slice.
I could eat breakfast.
- Huh! Yeah! Huh! Heh! Heh! Huh! Huh! Heh!
So, are you doing something tomorrow?
Yes, I am. Think about it.
Tomorrow, too? You'll think about it tomorrow? That kind of thing?
Well, I already...
I kind of have a list.I mean, I have a list.
I have a list of candidates.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
I really want this to go viral. I worked so hard on it.
Yeah, I did.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Okay, then.
Uh, Nutcracker.
Nutcracker.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Nutcracker, Nutcracker, Nutcracker.
Nutcracker, Nutcracker.
I knew it. You're all amazing, aren't you?
The name's Influenza.
Yes, it is.
It's true.
The influencer's name is...
The Nutcracker.
Yes, sir.
huh?
Mr. Takahashi is not an influencer after all.
The artist is Kazuki Takahashi.
That's totally different.
The Nutcracker is in his third year of college.
What? You're a college student?
So you'll be a senior this April?
You're all so young.
I see. And now you're trying your hand at gravure as well, and are also trying your hand at various things to appear in the Kansai Collection.
Influencer who is challenging various things to appear in Kansai Collection.
Are you also on TikTok, Nutcracker?
Yes, I've been on TikTok for about a year and a half.
I've been on TikTok for about a year and a half.
I've been a Nutcracker for a long time...
I'm totally fine.
From there, I'm a little more aware...
I see.
I'm totally fine on screen.
So, you're going to college and working as an influencer at the same time?
Yes. I'm really good at programming.
I'd like that.
So, Nutcracker, what kind of videos do you make on TikTok?
I'm uploading videos on TikTok, like "Azato Sexy.
I see.
Strong style.
I like that one.
How long have you been doing that?
About a year and a half.
That's great. I'd love to hear about it.
That's true.
There's a lot of people here.
Chaco.
Chaco is the "me-too" guy. He's been to the locations of popular TV dramas and movies.
He researches costumes...
He's an influencer who researches outfits and posts them.
What does this mean?
It's like the pilgrimage to sacred places that's popular now.
Like the pilgrimages to sacred places that are popular nowadays, like in dramas or places where the Johnny's go on location.
You actually go to the places where Japanese people have been filmed and post them on your website.
It's like a pilgrimage to a sacred place.
I see.
For people who don't get to go to places in the countryside, it's hard to go to places in Tokyo.
I can feel like I've been there.
That's exactly what the silent theaters are for.
The pilgrimage to the holy place got a lot of attention, didn't it?
That got a lot of attention.
Was that on TikTok?
That was on TikTok too.
Wow!
So many things are uploaded on TikTok, huh?
There's a lot of stuff on TikTok.
I'll check it out.
Every time we have a TikTok user on the show...
It's the first time we've had an influencer on the show.
We always have a lot of artists.I've always had a lot of artists.
I was wondering if you could help me out.
What is the gradation of what?
When I had nothing, I came up with an idea and thought, "I'm going to do this! I thought, "Let's do this!
Did you all start doing it?
How did you come up with the idea for this father and the others?
Well, I've always been a comedian.
Oh, really?
And he is a good talker.
Yes, he is.
It's just the way he says it that raises the bar.
Yes.
So, one with your father,
Oh, no.
I did a story about a rugby club member and his father,
And I played the role of the father,
The last tea was shirtless,
I was wearing a bra,
You know, like that,
I thought, "Oh, that's it.
That's how I got the character of the father,
Oh, if it was on TikTok.
I thought it would grow with the father character.
That's how it started.
- Wow. - I'm really sorry to hear that.
That's why comedians are the easiest to understand.
So you started when you were also a comedian?
After I finished being a comedian.
- After you were done as a comedian? - Yes, after I quit. Yes, after I quit.
Yes, after I quit, but it was a normal job, not a job,
You've been getting a lot of attention as a TikTok user?
- Yes, I did. I was ready to do it. - I was ready to do it.
Before I started TikTok, I was a VTuber and was broadcasting.
Wow. How long have you been a comedian?
I've been a comedian since I was in high school.
All of that happened so fast!
Doing it, quitting it, starting a new one, really fast!
- I'm only 23 years old. - Twenty-three years old.
I'm not quitting yet.
Current high school comedian.
- High school comedian. - High school comedian.
But that's why I'm in High School Bangs and stuff.
- Ah. - And I was also on the professional stage.
- I'm not in it now, but I was in underground shows. Yes.
- Oh, the kind of gigs where you could perform for free?
- Oh, yes. I'm already doing free gigs.
- That's true. I'd love to hear all about it.
- And now, I'm mainly on TikTok,
So you can live on that even though you live in Saitama?
- Yes, that's right. Yes. Well, there are times when I have to make ends meet, but...
- Wow.
- I can make a living. Yes.
- That's for sure. Amazing.
- The three of you in the whole row are complete artists.
- Ha-ha-ha.
- It's fresh, isn't it?
- So, here at the Nutcracker, we are university students, right?
- That's right.
- Yes, college students.
- That's right. I'm sorry, college students in the middle of the show. We'll talk about it later.
- I'll have them interact with the emulator.
- But there aren't that many college students who are doing well with Nutcracker, are there?
- It's not very common. It's not very common. I don't know anyone at my university.
- How did you get started, Nutcracker?
- I was watching TikTok and thought I'd give it a try.
- I was watching TikTok and thought I'd give it a try. So it's just like a certain college student's moves, right?
- And then my second video got about 950,000 views, and I thought it was fun.
- Then I started to work a little harder.
- Then I was approached by an agency or something like that.
- That's how it was.
- But it's still a bit of a life-changer.
- What are you going to do about this? I had a guy come to my show today, too.
- What are you going to do? What are you going to do when you graduate?
- That's really true, isn't it?
- You'll be job hunting this year, right?
- So you'll be job hunting this year, right?
- You'll be job-hunting this year, right?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
- What do you think? What do we do?- What do you think? What do you think?
- No, but you're looking for a job. No, but are you going to look for a job, or are you thinking about joining show business? Which is it?
- There are.
- And they are science majors.
- Yes, there are. And I just came from Kyoto.
- What?
- Yes.
- Yes. A university in Kyoto?
- Seriously?
I lived there all my life.
Yeah.
I'm not sure why I'm moving to Tokyo after graduation.
Are you looking for a job?
I'm not looking for a job, I'm looking to start my own business.
Oh?
Ah...
That's right.
That's so awesome.
Is that the programming kind? Or the influencer type classes?
Btw, it's kind of...
Tangled, that's...
I see.
Like the next generation of trendy apps that will replace TikTok, for example.
Wow.
I'd love to hear all about it, but I'm going to go with the theme now. That's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
Yes, you're right.
This is Talkin' Leap Corner. The theme is here.
Yes, sir. What I want New York to hear.
Eh?
Yes. Here's the first one.
I love YouTube.
Who is this?
We're looking for a name.
What is this? What do you mean?
I'm...
I love YouTube.
Mm-hmm.
It's time.
A little bit.
Scowling in my face.
Facepalm.
Time to go.
Why are you sitting in the front row?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Really.
Really
Why are you sitting in the front row?
really
Really
I'll know for sure.
I really do.
I swear.
You're gonna get in trouble.
No, no, no, I don't know.
I'm asking you right here, right here.
I'm just sitting here, if you don't mind.
I'm doing something bad.
I'm backing myself up.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
He said he loves YouTube so much.
He loves YouTube.
I love YouTube.
If I had more time
I write here on YouTube.
Well, you know.
If I can get YouTube...
I'll go on YouTube.
I understand.
I'll watch it.
Oh, my God.
Aww.
Uh...
And if you tell me your recommendation...
Recommendations
Yes, I do.Yes, sir.
He'll teach you.
There's three of them.
Yeah. - Okay.
Uh-huh.
The first one...
Mm-hmm.
Thank you very much, staff.
What's up, even the painting.
Mr. Canockster.
You okay with that?
I don't know. I'm... I'm... I'm... I'm Kanokstar.
It's not like this.
- Not like this? Not like this?
He's handsome, of course.
- Oh, my God.
Do you feel like you know them all already?
- I know, I know.
What about Mr. Chingyooji?
I have no idea.
- What?
- Mr. Tsinghui.
- I want it!
Mr. Chingachgook!
- Yes, sir.
- How old are you?
- I'm 39 now.
- That's not going to change.
- I see.
- That's why.
- Well, how about this?
- What do you recommend?
- Well, I mean, Cannockster, he's just so handsome.
- Oh, really?
- I don't like that picture then.
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay, let's see...
- Next.
- But there's something about the current animal.
Everything he says, everything. It's all so weird.
- Oh, it's not crazy, but you're that type of person?
He's that kind of guy. I saw him...
I was like, "Oh, it's okay to live like this.
- Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
- What kind of videos do you like the most? What kind of videos?
My favorite video.
- Recommendations, funny videos...
Let's see...
Strawberry Potatoes.
- You collaborated with Camocostar? Yes, that's right. Talk about someone you admire.
- The story of my dream.
- But I just checked and there are about 1.5 million of them.
- I see.
- I guess there are still people who don't know about it.
- I'll have a look.
- I'll check it out.
- Oh, that's right. It's very dirty. It's very dirty. That's...
- Does it get in?
- Yes, what I eat gets in.
- Do you eat strange things?
- No, really. No, really. I can tell when I see it.
- I can tell when I see them. Their behavior is crazy.
- I can tell when I see them. They act crazy.
- I see. That's good. What else?
- What else...
- LOL.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Mr. Shun.
Mr. Shun, calm down.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Flip.
Tokai On Air.
It's a little late for that, but this time it's Tokai On Air.
If it's Tokai On Air, it might be okay.
I know, it's messed up.
But what do you think?But how about
From the point of view of Mr. Name Wanted.
What do you recommend?
Tokai On Air is...
Tokai On Air.
I love the way they talk to each other, it's so funny.
Yes, that's right.
They are just so funny!
Hahahahahaha
No, it's okay then.
No, it's not.
If we do this...
I don't have it.
Ahahahahahaha
They're the best, right?
Three little girls, huh?
Ahahahahahaha
I don't know.
If you're that thin...
I'm sure Tokai On Air will say it's fine with us.
ahahahahahaha
But I'm writing arrows.
Well, for me...
Yeah.
I'm sure there are people who say
For sure.
I love them the most.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What do you like about him?
What do you like about Toshimitsu-san?
It's funny.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Next.
The next one's going to be great.
Joe Blogs.
I know what that is.
What's that?
We're from a generation where even we know a little bit about that.
Joe Blog has been around for a long time.
That's right.
You're a challenger. What's your point? The joe blog.
I learned how to challenge Joe Blog.
I see. So you're a bit of a blonde admirer too?
Yes, I admire blondes.
Oh, I see.
It's my ideal.
No way!
- But you're right... he's putting his body on the line.
- So you can't leave that out of it? The Tokai On Air Intelligence Unit?
- That's amazing! It's great. And there are people I don't even know.
- Thank you! Thank you!
- And here we go.
Yes, the self-proclaimed second fastest artist in the world.
- Here you go. Here you go...
- That's it.
- What's this?
- I like to run.
- I like running a lot.
- I like running a lot. I started it as a way to make live gigs.
- I see.
I'm hooked.
Oh, I see.
There was the Tokyo Marathon this year.
Yes, yes, the one the other day.
I got him to do it, and he finished in 2 hours, 50 minutes and 40 minutes, just under 3 hours.
Wow!
That's amazing!
2 hours 50 minutes, that's 270 minutes.
No, it's too fast for two hours.
Much faster, right?
That's crazy fast.
And the best artist right now...
Myron from The Pocket.
He's crazy fast.
Okay, wow.
About an hour and 34 minutes.
That's fast!
No one raised their hand, and I'm the second person to raise my hand.
Wow.
I see.I see.
Wow, that's great.
How many kilometers is that?
Two hours and 50 minutes.
Oh, four minutes.
That's less than 4 minutes. In terms of serve quality, I'd say less than 15 kilometers.
A serve-three is 34 kilos?
34 kilos.
Is there a tremendous wall here?
I would say serve-three is a percentage
of the running randoms.
It's about a single digit percent.
You're going to cut four?
Yes, I do.
Have you always been an athlete?
I hated running.
I hated it.
I never even ran track.
Did you play soccer? Yes, I played soccer.
I do play soccer.
How long have you been playing soccer? I started in 2017 or so.
But I'm still mostly playing.
I guess around 2013 or so. I went on my first car run in '18.
How often did you start out trying?
At first I ran 3 km or so. About once a week.
Isn't it still very hard?
It is very hard. I like to skip a lot.
I run slowly. I'm very lazy.
How does that spark?
I don't know. It just ignites all of a sudden.
I've never been on fire. Sometimes it does.
Suddenly there was a switch.
What's that?
The ranks dropped.
Maybe something like that.
How much do you run now?
I run when I have time.
About 120 minutes, I think.
What?
Like that?
Definitely.
What?
No, I have time for that.
When I'm working on a production, I'm pretty much at a standstill,
It's a mood swing.
How long do you run for 120 minutes?
Is it a long run?
120 seconds is 20 kilometers.
What?
I run about 6 tons.
No, but that's amazing.
What?
It's weird, I mean, if you're not running.
I feel really bad when I'm not running.
Has your body changed?
I started to make it so that I could do one- and two-hour gigs with all my strength.
I started to make myself do it, but now it's something else.
The introvert is an introvert with an introvert's stamina.
Did you have better things to do in the past, like getting out of bed and feeling good?
I'm five-tenths, so I don't really feel like I'm in good physical condition.
I'm five-tenths, so I don't really feel it.
I'm five-fifths, so I don't really feel it.
I'm getting up earlier, and I'm sleepy, and I'm hungry.
Then you can't sleep at night.
That's not good.
Sleep well
Health.
How's your weight and figure?
I haven't changed that much.
I don't run that much.
I've been doing some training, some strength training. I've been making him run a little.
Wow.
No, seriously, that doesn't mean much.
Awwwww!
You have to push it.
I'm gonna say it one more time.
I don't even do eggnog.
Oh, I won't do it.
Ew.Uh...
Wait a minute.
I see.
Before you run, or say, let's run in 10 more minutes,
Me, you know, sometimes I say, let's run at 9:30,
I'll do it at 10:00, after all.
I often say something like, "Let's run at 9:30," or "Let's run at 10:00, after all.
What is it about being in the zone?
Once I start running, I can't stop,
I feel like I can't pull out of the zone,
Let's just run for now.
So you don't like it before you enter the zone?
Sometimes I don't like it.
I see.
I'd like to go for a ride after the run.
Do you listen to music?
Wow, I listen to a lot of music.
You can listen to sound, right?
But that's a bit of a stretch,
You say "marathon.
No, but I'm a little shocked.
I don't think my body has changed at all.
That's for sure.
Well, I guess you weren't fat to begin with.
Maybe I was.
I used to have great physical strength.
Wow, a little.
No, but it's amazing that you can run a four-minute kilometer.
That's already possible if you work pretty hard on Thanksgiving or something.
That's for sure.
Yes, Thanksgiving.
That's amazing.
No, that's great.
Okay, well, let's continue.
Next, here we go.
What the hell is going on today?
What is it?
Dream Sir's muscle training.
He's an old man.
It's totally different from InkMaser.
They introduce YouTubers and stuff on InkMaser.
Nothing interesting.
They look at you, artists.
He sees reality, like an artist.
That's something that will definitely come later on.
It's a regional thing.
I'm going to run and do muscle training.
Did you go running, Mr. Nakajima?
Did you start strength training?
Yes, I do it every day.
Strength training every day?
I do it every day.
I feel like it changes my mind.
I feel more positive.
How long have you been doing it?
Five or six months.
Oh, so you weren't doing it when we met?
Not yet.
Okay.
What made you start?
Well, I'm 24 years old, and I'll be 8 this year,
I have never worked out before, not at all,
I've never worked out, I've never worked out at all, and I've lost weight by restricting my diet.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm not doing that, I can't keep up with it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, I've started a little bit.
Ah. So, what's it like? You go to the gym?
Uh, well, the gym is, uh, personal.
I go about once a week, and I went again today.
And the rest? I do the rest at home.
I would like to do personal training 5-6 times a week at home.
Definitely. Do you do it every day?
I do it seriously.
That's great. I think it's great that you can do it every day at home.
Do you buy dumbbells?
No, I don't. You weigh yourself?
No, I just use my own body weight.
Seriously, the most amazing people are the ones who can do that.
That's awesome.Wow.
How late are you doing this?
I was working on a project. Last year.
Just from this time last year.
Last year, I was really loose at home once a week. Now.
Ah.
So it really hasn't changed at all, or you know what I mean?
If I don't do it every day, that would make me feel bad, now.
It makes me feel bad.
I didn't get in that zone.
We were like, "Z-9 needs to finish up a little bit before this tournament," and we were like, "We're going to do it because we're in a hurry,
We were in a hurry to get it done before the tournament.
Maybe we weren't really into it.
That's right.
And when I did it once in a while, my muscles were sore as hell,
I couldn't do anything the next day, and I was sick of it,
Then I have to do it again for a month or so.
Ah, muscle training.
Do you have a goal? Like a goal.
No, I, uh, I have some kind of goal,
I've told my fans about it,
I want to shoot semiroutes.
Ah...
That's about right.
I see.
Every time.
I'd like to take a picture every time.
I see.
I'd like to take off my clothes and take some pictures.
Do you also eat?
I haven't been able to lately.
Do you eat a lot of protein?
Wow.
I'm not a big fan of shooting.
No, it's a swamp.
I'll do that forever.
But once I could hold the weight, I started to enjoy it.
Oh, I see.
If I do it now, I think I can get up to 90.
What?
Wow! That's amazing.
That's amazing.
That's some talent.
Ah.
I see.
Ah, it's a keeper though. It's exciting...but this kind of talk.
Hahahahahaha.
I go to a personal place, where comedians often come. Oh, wow.
He was there today, too. Hee... I don't know if I should say that.
I don't know if I should say so. Ah.
T-Malfon spoke.
T-Malfon?
You've done some muscle training?
I see. Well, well, well, well. I can see why you're into it.
Now, then, here we go.
Recommendation. The top 3 movies about the end of the earth.
Who is this?
Yes, that's me.
Ah! Mr. Kaiyu.
What is this?
I'm not really sick or anything,
I'm into movies where the earth is destroyed, and I've seen about 13 of them.
I'm watching about 13 of them.
I like the fact that it looks like it might actually happen.
You mean you don't mind if it doesn't have a happy ending?
Yes, that's right.
You mean you don't mind if they go away?
I want it to really happen.
Oh, you have to imagine something. Sure.
You mean if it really happens. That's true.
I can understand that.
I see.
Oh, I want to hear your recommendation. I want to hear it.
Please do.
Okay, third place.
So, there's a movie called Screen Land.
Oh, I don't know it.
You don't know it?
When was this movie made?
It's an old one.
Oh, wow.Heh.
I don't know.
Oh, I see.
I've been watching it a lot.
Screenland.
It's the type of movie where a meteorite falls and destroys the earth.
Oh, I see.
There are various types.
How is it destroyed?
Alien type?
Yes, yes.
Well, that's why.
Impact type.
You mean the Deep Impact type.
Yes, that's right.
And this one is about a comet falling to the earth.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
When was this movie made? I have no idea.
I don't know.
It goes back to the 1950s, doesn't it? I don't know.
Oh, the comet. That's right.
And the government, I don't know...they choose which families to help and which families not to help,
and evacuate them. I see.
I see. Oh, you mean that choice is interesting?
Yes, it is. The feeling of choosing.
It's kind of interesting to see how they stir each other up. I see.
That's interesting.
Yes, go on.
Yes, go on, go on. Do you know what the second one is?
No, I don't.
It's a mystery type.
Yes, mystery type.
Is this recent?
This one, well, it's a little newer than that.
Oh, so it's a panic/mystery type. What do you mean?
It's something from 50 years ago.
There was a piece of paper with the number of deaths and disasters written on it, and the number of the future written on it, and it was like, "Oh, the world is going to end.
I see.
It's like that.
Sounds interesting.
So, what's going to happen?
Well, that part.
Is that important? Should I not ask?
Spoiler alert.
Oh, yeah.
It's funny.
It's interesting, really.
Oh, wow.
Can we see it? Subscribe to it or something.
It's probably on Netfree or something.
Seriously? I'll have a look.
Sure. Next.
Number 1 is very famous.
Day Afters.
Ah, there it is.
I know it.
This is famous.
Have I seen it? What was it about?
It's a natural disaster.
Oh, natural disasters.
I haven't seen it.
But it's really famous.
It's a masterpiece.
It's about global warming.
Ah, global warming.
Oh, I see.
It sounds like something that might actually happen, and that's not good.
Oh, so that's why I'm really angry.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What's going to happen with global warming? Why is it so crazy?
The ice age is coming back.
Oh...
The ice age that killed off the dinosaurs.
What's really going to happen?
- Elsan is going to hit us with a huge tsunami or something.
Why did it have to be an ice age?
- Forgotten.
- You're the one who forgets.
- You know that everyone knows that when they meet you?
We don't know anything about it.
I guess you must be famous.You must be famous.
- I've seen 13.
I mean, I know all the first laws and stuff.
You know, like, what's the 13th?
I mean...
No, no, no, no.
I've only recently, you know, really recently figured it out.
You know, since I was a little girl.
It's not that big of a deal.
You've been giving me hugs lately?
Lately. Lately.
I see what you mean.
I just looked at the last three that I googled.
I liked these top three.
Three thirteenths.
I was wondering if it was a bad idea.
You asked me.
Maybe the best way to deal with it is...
No, no, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha
No, some movies you can't cope with and you'll die.
Maybe.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I see... Now then, let's continue. Here we go.
Mr. Kohei Otomo from Mr. Kohei Otomo. Now, what's this?
Oh, Mr. Wanishi.
Let's see, there's Kohei Otomo, right?
There's a song called "Rise." I've always loved it.
It's the opening song of an anime called "Major.
I see. I see.
That's why you are so young.
That's right.
And, well, I've succeeded in mastering it.
What?
I've mastered it.
Let me see. Show it to me.
The Kingdom Performance Challenge.
Ha-ha-ha.
But, um..,
If I go in the front, it's going to be a bit, you know, long.
That's right.
Ha-ha-ha.
Front-loading. Don't ever go. Front-loading.
I'm not going quietly anymore.
I want to go with the first arrival.
I want to go in the front suit.
That's great.
No, just give me the best part.
Uh, of course, of course.
Okay, then.
But, as a prerequisite, it's not a mimicry.
Oh, I see.
It's a mimicry,
I see.
This is new.
From Tomo Oh's performance,
I can be more like Tomo Oh and his performances,
It's not a monomaniac.
Strong and powerful.
I see.
What's that?
What an amusing excuse.
I see.
Well, I'll watch it anyway.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Will you recognize the song when you hear it?
Maybe. Maybe.
Okay, well, just the first chorus,
Yeah.
I'll let you know.
I'll teach you.
Both of you are in the performance.
Yeah.
Ah, you look a little different.Uh, you look a little different.
Uh, he's changing a lot.
Yeah.
Uh, not at all.
Holding a never-ending dream
Hold it close to your chest.
Running through it all.
The voice
To the big truth
Yes!
I see.
That's great.
- That's for sure. It's not this imitation, though. Really. It's really like your "automo kouhei" is the core of the song, like it's attached to you. It's like, it's not through your throat, but it's inside of you, it's like "automo fair".
But if I did this on TikTok, it wouldn't get any buzz.
Of course you wouldn't be able to raise it. Wouldn't it be great to launch or something?
I've been doing videos for about two and a half years now, and I've never sung a single song.
- I see what you're saying. I see. Anything is possible.
- Anything is possible. I've pioneered new people.
- I see. Why don't you try more things like that?
- Yes, that's right. TikTok is like this.
- Or even a woman. I don't sound like her, but even if it's perfect.
- If you really like them, you can do it. If you really like them, you can do it.
- With love alone.
- Is it automo fair?
Lasse is the only one who knows it.
You don't know any other songs?
Well, at least your own track?
That's good.
I'm not a Kohei Otomo fan.
I just like that song.
I like Rise a lot.
Then why don't you do it?
You're not a Kohei Otomo fan?
But you don't know that song?
I'm usually a huge Kohei Otomo fan.
Then I know why now.
It's just that song.
It's the best of Rise.
Okay, then, let's continue. Here we go.
What if... Yes, who's this?
Yes, it's me, Mr. Maemura
Yes, well, I'm often in a daze.
I often feel like if I had an infinite amount of money...
What if the Eastern Nervous System came in here?
I'm already, I'm already, I'm already...
I'm totally focused.
And so on and on and on and on.
I'm concentrating on it more and more. I'm like, "Oh my God, what if the Eastern Nerves come in here?
and then it becomes a song.
Wow.
When I was in high school, in class,
I kept thinking about the case of the Eastern Nervous System,
I was thinking about it all the time in high school.
But I got all red in the face,
Oh no, really.
Wow.
I was like.
Hee...
But it might be really important.
That's true.
You don't mess around with your phone much?
Oh, I do mess around with it,
Oh.
But when I think, "Oh, this is good,
I'm going to investigate it.
Oh, no, that's okay, I'll show you,
I don't have time for that anymore, that's for sure.
Ha-ha-ha.
Like before going to bed, when I can't sleep.
Before bedtime, sure.
If this happens.
I'd like to have sex with two messed-up women.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's impossible.
Impossible.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's impossible.
That's not possible.
That's not possible.That kind of thing.
That kind of thing.
Like direct video.
You forgot to think about that.
It would be a pornographic video.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, but I think about it before I go to bed.
That's the only time I think about it.
I think, "I'm back to my high school days with my brain,
I think.
Hmmm.
What would you do if you had it at home? I don't know.
It's like...
money?
No, it's...
I don't have any money.
I only like to talk about it when I'm in trouble and waiting for help.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Until you're dead.
Until you die, or when you're at your limits and there's nothing to do.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You mean if...
No, not about money.
Even the last Child, what?
I'd like to rent the Saitama Super Arena for a day.
I'd like to rent the Saitama Super Arena for a day, get all the fans together, have a little girl fling.
What's that?
Well, where are you spending the money?
Just for the place?
It's a lot of money just to rent a place.
And you don't have to pay for the tickets?
I think the fans would be happy if the tickets were free.
Not many come.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I see.
If Maemura-san doesn't sing, not many people will come.
He doesn't come very often.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
You can do whatever you like without limit, right?
But, in terms of money, doesn't it make you feel lonely?
I don't know, maybe you don't think so much of it? I wonder if this is a possibility...
In conclusion, we finally came to the conclusion
Ah, it's all in the imagination.
If you imagine too much money in your imagination, you will end up with
I don't know, maybe I don't think about it.
Then you think, "If I had that money, I could do this.
And then you think, "If I had that money, I could do this, and I could do that, and I could do that.
And then you end up thinking
Oh, I think it would be good if I could sell it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'll do it.
I end up in a bat that says I should work harder.
Ah!
I can't stand up to the bat.
That was Chaink.
I shouldn't have done that.
Certainly to the bat, certainly.
So, even if I had the money to do this and do that.
I don't know if I'd enjoy it, huh? I mean...
It doesn't matter if I make money.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Sometimes I go to bat.
So what's the bottom line?
Sometimes, you know, you get in that zone.
Who would you like to see come in here?
Who would you like?
I'll come in with someone.
Okay, I'm going to go to the "Who's Your Favorite Person?" presentation.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Good night. Good night.
Good night, good night.
A little rude, guys.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
First of all
Everyone, there are only artists.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What should I say to them first?
Uh...Uh...
I wonder what would make him happy, this guy or that.
Oh.
And, uh, it's okay.
That's true.
But I used to think about that kind of thing more when I was in school.
That's right.
I think my brain is getting worse and worse.
But that's wonderful.
If you think about it and realize that you can do it...
That's a good thing.
It's good to think about it all the time.
You might think about it a lot.
Recently, I've been thinking about if I were a job hunter.
To the point where I'm taking the entrance exam tomorrow.
I've been living in a really nervous state.
My imagination was so intense.
Not before going to bed or anything.
All day long.
Tomorrow's the interview.
Oh, it wasn't a job interview.
Adults are bakay.
It was one before, until I was a student taking an exam.
I wrote a song dedicated to students taking exams.
I'm a student who's taking an entrance exam.
It's the national common exam on that day.
I was so nervous about that day.
But you didn't study, right?
No, I didn't.
I'm just nervous, but I'm not studying.
That's funny.
And then the staff said to me.
They said, "Mike Rasta isn't a student for the exam either.
Like an actress who really plays the part.
It's true.
We can all do songs together, so there are days and so on.
Ahhh.
But is it suitable for ZWIM or something like that?
I mean, if you can't write songs, it's too meaningless.
That's right.
He's a pain in the shoulder, isn't he?
He's a very bad person.
No, I'm just saying he's a great talent. I'm glad.
Okay, let's continue.
Here's the next one.
I met Shimazato when I was a comedian.
What?
Ola, what's this?
Who is this?
That's me.
Oh, Chako, you used to be a comedian too?
Former comedian.
Yes, I am.
I did one of Mama Tart's.
Who is your agency?
It was Sun Music.
Oh, wow.
How many years did you work there?
Only 5 years.
But not at all.
So you are an influencer from a comedian?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Oh, wow.
So you've been doing it all at the same time?
While being a comedian and an influencer?
I was doing it in the second half of the year, around 2019.
Like making a pilgrimage to this holy place?
Oh, I'm doing that.
I was originally imitating RYOTA CAPEES of the GENERATIONS.
I was uploading a video imitating Capellas Ryota of the GENERATIONS.
Oh, I see.
That's a good-looking guy.
Then, I was beaten up.
Beaten?
Didn't it get any buzz?
Yes, it did.
Did you get buzz, but did you get beat up?
They hit me hard.
They were very passionate about it.
But I did appear in Kohaku and other places with my impersonation.But in case you are wondering, that moniker has appeared in Kohaku and other places.
That's great.
You must be a whacker.
That's right.
It pisses you off, doesn't it?
That's right, you slap them.
A guy who beats people up.
They're shitty, right?
That's right.
Ah.
- It's really good. So? What about Mr. Shima?
You say you saw Mr. Shima? Oh, really? That's right.
What is it? This. Well, I used to live in Koenji.
Oh, that's Mr. Shima. That's it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha. Let me talk.
Oh, Koenji, 100% you. You're the only guy like you in Koenji.
Please let me talk. Oh, you live in Koenji?
Yes, I did. For about 5 years. I lived there for 12 years.
Yes, yes. Until a year and a half ago.
You see that Dairy crosswalk on the right side of the north exit?
Yes, yes, yes. Out the north exit? There is that Dairy on the right after the north exit.
That's where Kanagawa or something like that is. That's right. There's The Kohenji and so on.
And when I was walking in the pedestrian crossing there, I saw Mr. Shimassa with his eyes wide open like this.
I didn't look at him. On the other side? I didn't look at him. I really didn't.
I really didn't see him. I don't often go to the other side, but sure.
No, really. That was Mr. Shimassa. Were you drunk?
No, it was during the day. During the day?
When? During the day.
When? How many years ago? About 4 or 5 years ago.
Four or five years ago? That's quite a while ago, but... Well, around 2018 or 9, I guess.
Yes, about 20. But that was when Mr. New York was still at the top of the list at Infinity. At that time.
Four or five years ago? I don't know. I was over there once,
If they take away my bike, they'll take it all over there. Oh, that?
Yes, that's right. It's over there. It was there, it was there.
Across the tea plantation. I was pissed off because I couldn't get it back for some reason.
When I came back, I did it. It was painful!
That's for sure. It was so hard. Then Shimassa was already waving his side arm.
I was so bummed out.
Oh, my God, something was moving the bike to a different place. Oh, that sounds like it.
Something must have cost a lot of money or something, when they couldn't get the bike back.
I wondered where it went after that. I wondered where he went in that state of shock.
I'm crazy about it. Maybe that was it. Maybe that was me then.
Wow, that feels good. It's all connected.
I know this doesn't happen, but I'm pretty sure I wouldn't remember it, so shimmy, shimmy, shimmy.
Okay, well, I have some final announcements from our guests. First of all, Gladio.
Gladio: Yes. Tomorrow, May 3, we have a full album.
Start Sports Magic has also come out with the funkiest album, so please check it out.
We will have another footprint in July, so please come and visit us.
July is for real.
Mr. Maemura.
Yes, I am. My new album Sai was released on May 7.
That's great, the album.
I have a national tour starting at the end of May.
I also have a live concert in the U.S. coming up at the end of May.
Wow!
Where are you going?
Chorus City,
What?
Nahkolefest,
Nahkolefest.
It's a stadium culture festival,
I'll be there,
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing you there.
Oh, wow.
You've got it.
Well, let's start from the latter half of May,
If you were an American, right?
Yes, I would be.
I would be an American.
No, that's it.
No, I'm imagining it when I go to America.
What? You became an American?
Mr. Takahashi, I'm counting on you.
Yes, I will. Well, I've been doing the Rojon Live almost...
I do it every day.
What?
Yes, sir.
That's amazing.Holy shit.
Seriously?
And you train your muscles every day.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
One time.
Wow.
That's great.
So, yes.
I'm doing it in Shinjuku or something.
If you'd like.
Oh, wow!
We're looking forward to seeing you.
Wow!
That's great!
Applause.
Seriously.
That's great.
Okay, Mr. Waniti.
Okay, um...
I designed this T-shirt.
I designed the T-shirts that are not for sale.
Is now on sale.
I'm so happy!
Welcome!
Please wear it.
Oh, sure.
Ha-ha-ha!
Not this one?
Not this one.
I can't believe I just said that.
That's messed up.
That's the one that makes me the angriest.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Not this one.
Oh, and, um...
I'm asking you to buzz me.
and that YouTube show called
I also did a YouTube show
I've been doing it for a while now.
I'm looking forward to it.
You do a lot of things.
What is your name?
Yes, um...
I'm...
My goal for this year is 1 million total social networking followers.
- I see. Yes, yes, yes. If you like, YouTube, TikTok,
If you like, please click the follow button on YouTube, TikTok, and Instagram, and the subscribe button on your channel.
- Please do. Congratulations! One million.
Now, let's move on to the Nutcracker.
Okay. I'm doing a photo book, my first photo book,
It's coming out in June or July.
- A photo book? A photo book? A photo book?
- Yes.
A college student!
A college student on Instagram.
I'll announce it on Instagram with stories and stuff.
Please follow us if you like!
Next, Chaco!
Yes, I'm the one in the T-shirt!
Pilgrimage to the Holy Land T-shirt!
No, no, no.
Stop being a comedian T-shirt
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't care.
Shikan no
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's totally fine.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hey, hey, hey!
It's a pilgrimage T-shirt.
It's like that Givenchy T-shirt.
It's like a brand-warming T-shirt.
I see... you've said it all.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's good. That's good.
I'm on a pilgrimage to a holy place on TikTok and Instagram.
I'm also making a pilgrimage to the Holy Land on TikTok and Instagram, so please do!
I look forward to working with you all!Nice to meet you all.
That's kinda funny, Mr. Ink Racer's story.
I want to see, see, see.
I really wish I could have heard a lot more.
So thank you all very much.
Thank you very much.
Wow, that's great.
- Amazing. Good music. Thank you very much.
- I knew it, but it's really various.
- You sell T-shirts.
- But Takahashi is now a solo artist, too, and he's doing it every day.
- Hey. Hey, do you perform at Roger's every day?
- That's true.
- So those two used to be comedians.
- Yes, they used to be comedians.
- Amazing, isn't it?
- Well, Mr. Wanishi, I guess you did a little bit in high school.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, like that.
- If there are college students, too.
- There are college students, too.
- There are all kinds of people.
It's fun to hear stories from people who are not artists.
Now, let's continue,
Sorry for the wait.
Here they are, the guests of the third part, the engine crew.
Yay!
Thank you very much, Engine.
Thank you very much.
The engine is 9 people, really 9 people, who are pursuing their dreams, right?
That's right.
Connecting the circle that met the engine full throttle, drawing a circle, and putting the engine together,
Together with our fans, we will create music on a new stage,
The nine members, who are active in various genres, fuse singing, dancing, and acting,
We are a hybrid performance unit.
Thank you very much.
Could you introduce yourself, please?
Uh, yes.
Yes.
Ah, yes.
From today, I would like to introduce your prince, Yoshiaki Kusaji-Yamada.
Yes, Kusaji-kun.
Good morning.
Yes, I'm Kumako and Fumiya Kumazawa.
I'm Kumako and Fumiya Kumazawa.
Yes, I'm Fumiya Kumazawa.
Yes.
Well, the name is distant.
Well, but your distance is close, I am Kazusei Takatani.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're greeting him well, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
That's amazing.
I didn't know they were that close.
They were about as close as a group of girls.
Ha-ha-ha.
It was there.
That's for sure.
It was a group of guys.
That's rare these days.
Ah.
Enjin is going to be Yoshimoto, right?
Yes, that's right.
We often practice at the head office.
That's right.
Ah.
Last time, exactly one year ago, during the Golden Week holidays,
Yes.
There was a lot of "Laughing Future Fest" and I wanted to show it to us.
That was exactly one year ago, right?
Yeah, exactly one year ago.
Exactly one year ago.Exactly one year ago.
This past May.
Wow, a lot of big festivals and stuff.
It's true, it's true.
I watched Produce 101 Japan.
You were there, weren't you?
Yes, that's right.
And how about you, Sol?
We had dinner once or twice.
Yes, that's right.
And the engine?
Yes.
Wow.
That's right.
Oh, the market one.
The market one. That's right.
I see.
It's not often that I get to talk about engines like that with such gusto.
Indeed.
Well, I would like to talk with you.
Thank you very much.
The first topic is this.
I would like to talk about the engine and what kind of group it is.
Engines?
Engine? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Engines.
It's with the engine.
Oh.
What? Why?
Three.
With carrots.
Oh, with carrots.
Thank you.
It's easy to remember.
Engine.
Okay, well, here's the first one.
The 3 best things about engines.
I'd like to spy on you for a moment.
Tell me, what is this?
Yes.
Nakabayashi-kun taught me this.
Yes. This is to let more and more people know the appeal of the engine.
I want more and more people to know the charm of the engine,
I would like to introduce it to you.
I'm going to introduce them here.
The first one is here.
Here it is.
There you go.
Nakayoshi.
Cute.
Yes!
This is really... No matter where I go to work...
I'm often told by the staff that the engines get along well with each other.
Suddenly everyone gets along?
That's right.
Wow.
Even in the dressing room, there is really no silence,
Everyone is talking all the time,
Even the clients go out to play with each other.
Yes, that's right.
After every rehearsal, we would go out to eat with someone downstairs.
That's a good thing.
But they are really good friends.
- There are a lot of young groups. They don't seem to be fighting too much. But I imagine that when there are nine people in a group, there is a kind of, what do you call it? There are no factions, but there is no such thing, and there are no fights between any of them, or between any of them, or between any of them.
- It was just the three of them.
- No, but maybe that is because we all came from audition programs, and the bond that we have formed through our many years of experience together is probably very strong.
- It's really like a school, isn't it?
- Yes, like in a club.
- But, as you can see, all nine of us who were not so involved during the audition period are now together.
- Oh, I see.
- We were all from different backgrounds, so there was a sense of distance between us.
- But we were all from different backgrounds, so there was a sense of distance between us.
- For about two years.
Ahhh...
I see.
Even on your days off?
Okay, so basically, do you have a lot of days off?
Everyone is off...Everyone's off...
Yes, that's right. So, our vacations are pretty varied.
Oh, so it's all scattered.
That's right. Like today, I had some time off the other day.
I'm not interested in both of them and their clothes.
Oh, I see.
Wow.
Not at all.
Really?
I see.
So, no.
I'm pretty much dressed like a pince-nez.
Smile.
No, I don't.
You know, sometimes he's good-looking and I knew it.
Yes, they are.
I see.
They're so good-looking that they get blunted by their clothes.
That's right.
And if you meet a fan or something...
I wouldn't like it if I looked tacky.
I see.
That's why.
I don't want to look tacky.
That's right.
The one that comes with an engine.
And... we'll go and pick one out together, and...
That would be nice.
Yes, that's good.
Wow.
So you were shopping.
Yeah, we were.
You know, we work with orbs a lot.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What about Orb? Do you get along?
You don't like him much?
Orb.
I don't,
I only see him once in a while.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, that,
Between you and your wife,
Do you go out together sometimes?
We don't go out together,
We don't go out for fun, but the other day we just happened to go,
I like sauna,
I like saunas, and we were taking a bath,
I was taking a bath,
I was taking a bath, and in front of me was Kazu Kun.
He came in,
Oh, wow.
He was talking a bit.
That's great.
I knew he was a member of the headquarters before the tele.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ah, a member of the head office.
From the front office.
No, no, no.
Don't say that much in English.
I'll explain it to you.
What do you mean?
I don't know,
Like we went to school together?
Yes, it's like that.
We're separated now,
I'm doing my best, but..,
But you are like that?
That's exactly how it is.
Wow.
Honda, you are strange.
We were in a group on the show.
We were performing in a group together.
Oh, I see.
You've done a lot of things in time.
I see.
It's kind of like a long-armed mix.
And then things got a little crazy at the end.
It's a red pee-pee.
Is this still number three?
Yes, followed by...Yes, followed by.
Here is the second place. Well, then!
Kose!
What?
It's like the first greeting.
Each and every one of you
Each and every one of you has your own greeting.
And then there are some members who are in the fashion grand
Some of the members are in the fashion field.
If you are called "Kumachan," you are a voice actor.
or a voice actor.
And then there's this one who's really good at beauty.
And there is this girl who is really good at beauty.
and there's this girl who's really good at beauty, and there's this girl who's really good at
And this clip is all designed and drawn by Kumachan.
She designs and draws all the clips.
She also designed and drew some of the goods.
He also drew some of the goods.
You made him draw them?
That's right.
Even though it's in the clip section.
I just did.
Draw a bear.
Yes, I knew that each and every one of you
Even if they debut as solo artists...
I wanted each one of them to have enough individuality to stand out as a solo artist
That was our motto.
That's what we were working on.
For live performances
I was in charge of
I'm in charge of stoicism and
And I also do acrobatics
I also do acrobatics live.
I see.
Yes.
That's Solofon, too.
He's also really good at karate.
That's right.
Wow!
The world's
- I'll say it later.
- Oh, I see.
- I'm certainly curious.
- I mean, second place is individuality.
- And, you know, first place.
- First place. Yes.
- Ta-da! Live!
- I think this is the real thing.
- Straight to the point!
- No more twists and turns for another person.
- It's so straight.
- Straight!
- Straightforward.
- Straight! Straight! Straight!
- It was direct.
- It said "love, beauty, goodness, peace.
- The best principle.
- Yes, that's right.
- I guess so.
- You know, the fans the most.
- We call ourselves muse.
- Why muse?
- MU3E is written "MU3E".
- It's 3E.
- We are three circles.
- We are three circles, and we are the guests, the staff, and the staff, Naoku.
- Naok, the staff, and the fans.
- And the fans are the three circles.
- Muse was originally God.
- God.
Um, yes.
The nine gods of the garden.
Um, the nine gods for each of the arts.
That's called a muse.
Heh!
It's called muse with three sides.It's called a muse with three sides.
It's not "customer god," but it's a muse made up of many things.
I see.
That makes a lot of sense.
Ah, I see.
It also contains the character for "God.
Yes. It's for the engine.
Everyone at Muse tells me that the live performances are the most fun.
I see.
And that's part of our personality,
We make everything from the setlist to the direction,
We make everything ourselves, from the set list.
Wow.
Didn't Mr. Yashiro direct some of the performances?
Oh, that's right.
Ah, Mako Yashiro-san.
Oh!
That's important.
So I heard there's going to be a play.
Like the first introduction.
I'm more than just a regular idol.
So it's really something.
A lot of things.
- I think of it as doing something. Acting. That's right.
I also incorporate those elements into my live performances,
I see.
We are particular about live performances that only we can do,
That's why we chose live performance as the first place.
That's very meaningful.
That's true.
Next, let's continue,
Then, please do it.
Please do.
No, no, I want to go.
Daisuke Yoshimoto, you can go.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'll go.
I'll be there.
So, here we go.
Yeah.
Secrets that even the fans don't know are out in the open.
I like it.
Because Daisuke's top three are still Dokyokkyo.
Ha-ha-ha.
Really?
I'm good friends with my mom.
Ha-ha-ha.
Who is this?
This is me.
Huh.
Actually, I've gained 10 kilos since I joined the engine.
Eeeeeee!
Indeed.
Indeed, indeed.
Oh, seriously.
You're definitely a little rounder.
I thought it might be because my hair is getting higher.
No, but no way.
You've lost 10 kilos looking like that?
Yes, 10 kilos.
But it's totally fine.
It's totally fine, but it's not good.
Yes, it is.
How long have you been a comedian?
About two and a half years.
I haven't gained 10 kg in two and a half years as a comedian.
Ha-ha-ha.
Almost all comedians gain 10 kilograms.
That's for sure.
That would be the people who are really fat already.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's bad, this Heisei era.
Yes, that's right.
Because they are idols.
Why, because, yes.
Why, why?
No, what is it?
I mean, you know, college kids, you know.We did college students and stuff, you know.
Oh, yes.
I remember so much, though.
I remember. I remember.
I mean, we were like a team of hot college guys, right?
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
It's like, you know..,
I know.
It's stress, isn't it?
Stress.
Hey, don't say it, don't say it, don't say it.
Hey, we're good friends.
We're doing this as good friends.
That's true.
We're good friends.
We are good friends,
I guess there is a lot of stress outside of the group.
I see.
Well, when you enter this world, there is a lot of pressure,
There are some things you don't get used to.
You have to let your guard down.
When you eat,
I'm going to order two servings of the main course.
I'll definitely order two portions of the main menu.
That's not really a good idea. No, no.
That's just now, even though you're young.
But, you know, it's not good. Nonaka-kun told me to lose weight,
I've been on a diet lately.
Oh, I see. Well, I've been on a bit of a diet,
I've lost 5 kilos.
No, no, no, I'm scared. The way you gain weight and lose weight... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So you're 5 kilos lighter than you were when you first started?
You're five pounds lighter now than you were when you were at your peak weight?
Oh, yeah. From peak. Oh.
Oh, I see. That's right.
Now, to put it another way, I gained 12 or 3 kilos.
So, now you've gained 7 kilos,
So you've lost 7 kilos?
No, but a lot. But a lot.
Well, that's a lot of work, huh? What did you lose weight on? Did you lose weight from eating?
Well, muscle training, learning, and, you know,
I don't eat too many carbs.
I eat a portion.
No, I'm just saying, you know, now's a good time. Seriously.
I don't know.
You said you were skinny back then. Oh, yes. I was skinny.
But you were skinny, too. You know, quite a lot.
You know, with the idol's companions, they were all, generally...
That's right.
Now, I feel like I'm just fine.
You have to be careful about being alone too much, you know.
It's the engine.
An engine. Maybe it's the engine.
It's an engine. It's an engine.
That's right. Okay, well, let's continue.
Next, this way.
The nail is...
What's this?
Well, I'm often seen as slender,
That's true. That's true.
I think it's a strange information.
People call me a bean sprout, but I'm actually good at tennis, and I've been to the national championships.
Oh, so you are a sportsman.
Not only me, there are many people who are good at engine sports,
That's right. I played soccer for my school and went to the national tournament.
Oh, that's right. You both played in a national championship?
Yes, we did.
That's great.
And you, Sol, you play karate, right?
Yes, I am.
Yes, sir.
You're talking about Injuner.
That's for sure.
That's amazing. So it was all black and white?
Yes, I did.
Oh, I see.
I was always very black.
Wow.
I see.I see.
In my high school and junior high school, we all had to work a hell of a lot of hours.
That's why they were all so black.
That's right.
You know, like burnt bread.
Ha-ha-ha.
Under-baked kotatsu.
I see.
Yes.
I see. Then it would be nice if there was something that would let me go to something like that.
That's right.
It's not like it's on TV.
No, something like that.
No, I think we'd be lost if we went to that kind of thing.
Now, there are no long programs like that.
There was no soccer.
Do you still play soccer?
I still go to futsal sometimes,
I play futsal with Sol.
Wow. But to go all over the country, that's a pretty high level, isn't it?
It's not half bad.
To be honest, you are pretty good at it?
Yes, he was. To be honest.
In what prefecture?
In Osaka.
What? Isn't that a mess? Going all over the country in Osaka?
Yes, that's right. The level was really high.
Yes.
Did you play tennis next time? Tennis now.
I don't play tennis at all now.
I see.
I'll take care of it.
Well, next time we play with Traugtavas.
I'll invite you when I play with Masai and others. I won't. There.
Mamos, Watanabe, and others.
I'm doing Tabas with comedians that no one knows, and I don't call them angels.
I want to call them.
There is not much that is different.
Okay, then, I'll continue with this one.
What I'm into these days. What is this?
Tell me. Masai, Mamos.
What?
Masai, not rice?
Not muscle training?
It's more of a hobby.
I want to know!
What are your top 3 hobbies these days?
You're going to tell me your top 3?
First of all, number 3!
Blue Rock.
It's a comic book!
Only the really gaga egotists are gathered in Blue Rock.
The cartoon?
The cartoon.
Original text.
It's really interesting.
I know it too...
This...
Nagi Seishiro
Yes, yes, yes...
I'm sorry, but...
Yes, yes...
Exquisite.
By the way, did you draw that picture in the meadow?
I did it.
Oh, good, good, good.
Have you been...
You've been doing this?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm really, really...
I'm always tired.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Love.
Sometimes, a character like that
Sometimes they're geniuses.
I only got about halfway through the show.
It's fun.
Is it on now?
It's in production now.It's in the current series.
So this is the kind of high school soccer story I was talking about.
High school.
Yes, all fords.
And they're locked up in a facility called Bull Rock.
And if they don't like it, they go home.
It's not a reality show about love.
And if they go home, they have to stop playing soccer.
Uh-huh.
Are you still in that building?
No.
No, he's not.
He's out for a while.
Ha-ha-ha.
But he's in there.
Just in case.
Oh, really?
How many people live in that building?
That's right.
Oh...
Is this where he's going to fall?
- I see. So I didn't say goodbye to the character I fell in love with.
- I see. I'm not going to come out anymore.
It's a place that was created by someone who is that crazy.
It was a place made by a person who was a little bit crazy.
- Ah, listen to me.
- Please listen to me.
- Well, I'll go back and read it again.
- If I read it now.
- It's a real hot topic right now.
- I'm going to listen to it now.
- No, I've heard of it. I've heard it so much.
They say they are doing it many times now.
- Wow.
He's said it quite a lot.
It's about 160 episodes.
160 episodes.
We're going to do it in episodes.
Who's going with the story?
It's a cartoon.
I'll go on to the second best.
Oh, wait, best two.
I don't want that. I don't want that.
What's that? I don't want that.
Do you want some?
Worst. Worst.
Don't diet.
What is that? Is that like a cheat day?
Or are you into diet food?
No, I mean, really, that's what it is.
I haven't been eating lately.
Have you been holding back lately?
I've been really patient lately, but really...
But since we can't let this one go, here it is in second place!
What do you usually do for dinner?
We ate out yesterday, and my mom said, "No, don't eat any more.
My mom told me to stop eating, and she offered me some, but it wasn't enough, so I ate alone in the fridge.
I eat my meals alone in the fridge, and then I listen to her and eat.
- High school kids. High school?
I still didn't gain weight in high school.
- Ah. I see. What do you like? Rice.
I like potatoes.
- Potatoes? You like potato food?
I love it.
- Do you think potato food is fattening? I like french fries.
Oh, you're munching, aren't you?
Oh, right, carbs.
Carbohydrates.
I see.
Ah.
Okay, then. Number one.
Yes, number one.
What did you make?
It's Mr. Pen around the corner.
I don't need this.
Best first place.
I don't want it.
I don't want this.
This way, please.
Ah!Ah!
It's Real Escape Game!
Oh, you're into it.
I love it.
Heh.
I was into it for a while.
Since now?
The keynote of the system.
No, I was into it.
I wasn't invited.
You didn't invite me.
I'm not into it. You are.
I am, I have. Oh, who are you going with?
This is also me, and I'm really going to invite my friends and stuff.
Oh, seriously, let's go.
No, thanks,
No, you haven't been. It's been too long.
But he invites me a lot.
Hmm, actually, yes, so we're locked in a locked room,
And then you have to unscramble all the images in that locked room and get them out,
It's fun, isn't it?
You know, maybe even a little haunted house type thing,
I've seen it before.
Yeah, the three of us.
Just the three of us.
Mr. Asahi?
No, um, Shinjuku.
Shinjuku.
Heh.
That's it.
But that's the kind of thing you can't do without a few people.
Well, yes.
Even if you are a member, you go there once in a while.
That's right.
We make time for it.
The three of us go together.
I see.
The horror stories are amazing.
So each one of us hides in a locker.
Aah! Oh! Yes, yes, yes.
I've got that kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah.
It's really scary.
I'm really scared.
That's where that ghost guy played.
That locker guy walked by.
Yeah, scary.
And then me and Bear's locker went by.
And there was Toy's locker.
Yeah, scary.
And right after that
I heard a scream
I heard a scream I've never heard before
And there was a scene.
Yeah.
And the lockers are all together.
I don't know if they're there.
And then it was like, "Oh, no, I'm in.
Yeah.
So, Toy, your locker.
Don't hide with the girls... that was great.
You're a New Yorker, when it comes to girls.
Okay, well, I guess that's the last one. Let's go. This way.
I want to ____ with New York. Who is this?
Yes.
Yes, this is Mr. Kumazawa.
Kumazawa-san,
Kumazawa-san.
Um, an event..,
Yes.
Well, it's the same with live performances.
I guess, you know, you have to make a gag at the end.
Yes.
There are a lot of performances.
No, that's...that's...that's something.
Ha-ha-ha.
Why?
There are a lot of them.
Why do you call them idols? That's what they say, but that's it.
Why don't you do that already?Why don't you do that anymore.
Oh, come on, guys.
Why?
That's the way it's supposed to be, huh?
Yeah.
Are you being taken advantage of?
No, it's my job.
Oh.
No, it's not. Everyone says so.
Because, you know, idols,
I want a gag. I want a gag.
I don't know why.
So, that's why.
You don't do the same thing with comedians, right?
I don't think it's the opposite of a comedian's gag.
I don't care if it's a denge, but the point is, we have to think together.
Well, but Kaguya Haneru is already, really.
You know, one-hit gags for idols, you know.
I've already given it to you.
I'm counting on you to give it a shot.
What's this?
The one with the engine?
Three.
Three is hard.
Three is fine.
Four is good.
Four is fine
I can think of nine more.
All of them.
Stop time.
He wants nine.
On behalf of the group.
What do you want?
I don't care. I like you.
Kumazawa?
Kumazawa-kun.
Basically, you want Kumazawa.
Well...
He's got a pretty face, that's for sure.
He's gotten a lot cuter.
What?
You memorized it? That face.
I remember. I remember. It wasn't on location like this.
Oh, it wasn't?
Uh-huh.
Let's see...
Uh-oh.
Oh, my God.
I think I've got an idea.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I do.
What is it, Kumazawa? Kumazawa-kun?
Kumazawa-kun's?
Yeah.
Oh, great.
But I'm going to need everyone's help.
Combination?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna use your hair, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
It's long, isn't it?
Yes.
Like, uh... like bear ears.
Like bear ears.
Yeah.
Like, cute, like... Oh, yeah, like bear ears.
Cute, cute, cute. Turn around.
Turn around. Turn around.
Turn around once.
Is that a bear?
Is that a bear? Those ears...
Is that a bear? Is that a bear? I said...
I turned around.
Oh, it's a bear, isn't it?
You wanna give it a shot?
You'd look like a bear, right?
What? Is that a bear?What's that? Is that a bear?
It's a bear.
It's definitely a bear.
No, it's not a bear.
It's a bear sushi!
Wait a minute, I haven't caught up yet.
Anyway, let's go. Let's just go for now, shall we?
Let's not do that.
What was that?
Oh, my God.
I just thought of something. I can't believe I just thought of that.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Laughs.
Laughing.
LOL.
LOL!
One more time, then one more time, just one more time.
Laughter.
All you have to do is stand up one more time.
Huh?
That's not a bear.
It's a bear.
It's not a bear.
It's Mr. Bear.
Mr. Bear.
Mr. Bear!
Hey.
No, sir.
You've got an idea.
It was Kwaman.
What?
Oh, my God, I'm gonna have to stop.
I'm quitting. I'm quitting.
I'm gonna stop.
I'm getting fucked up.
I'm serious.
What's that? It's a bear.
Huh? It's a bear.
He moved his hair and did something.
Huh? It's not a bear.
A little more bear-like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
On the head.
I'm a bear. I'm a bear.
I'm a bear.
A bear?
No, it's not a bear.
Tskagechii...
Bear.
I'm a bear.
You're too Yoshimoto. Everything that's wrong with Yoshimoto is out there.
Let's stop. I won't play one more game.
It's horrible.
You really shouldn't do it. You should refuse.
Tell him to do it already.
I see. I said, "Let's do it," but the preschooler...
The guy who's not on his feet.
They're going to make us perform.
It was like hell.
Until then, the live performance was great. Then, at the end...
I'm telling you the truth.
So, I have an announcement from the kindergartners.
Yes, I do.
Thank you very much.
Yes, we are June 15th, 7:00 p.m.
- Are you there? Yes. Yeah. - Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah. Yeah. - EX Theater, Roppongi
- Well, we're actually in the middle of a tour, and we're going to play the final show at this venue...
- Oh, the finals. Yes, at the EX Theater.
- Oh, yes, the final will be held at the EX Theater. - June 15 is also our 3rd anniversary.
- Already the third anniversary?
- That's right.
- That's right. Oh, I see. But also the oven.
- It's going to be a special show.
- I see. I see. And so is the oven.- I see. So is the oven.
- Ah, it's been that long already.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- That was fast. Amazing.
- That's right.
- I see.
- So, please join us, Mr. New York.
- June 15?
- Yes, June 15.
- Certainly.
- I'd like to go if I can.
- By all means.
- June...
- June 4th? I doubt it.
- Yes, it is.
- June 4th?
- It's one or the other.
- I'm almost out of tickets.
- Oh, wow.
- If you're interested, please bring your neighbor.
- I want to go.
- I want to go, but....................
- I'd love to go, but....
So, to all the performers, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Well, that's all for today.
Well, I have talked about many things.
I talked to 20 people.
Well, it was a gorgeous event, wasn't it?
I mean, it was even more gorgeous than before,
I still have more to say.
I'm sure. I wish I could have talked to each and every one of the influencers,
I wish I could have dug into each and every one of them.
Ah....
That's all for now,
I wonder what kind of people will be coming next month.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope you will pay attention to how many people will be coming.
That's all for today's Tokyo Award. See you next time.
Bye!